Joachim	B-PER
III	I-PER
of	I-PER
Constantinople	I-PER

*2004	O
:	O
My	B-ORG
Wife	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Kids	I-ORG
''	O
...	O
.	O
Childcare	O
Instructor	O
(	O
1	O
episode	O
,	O
2004	O
)	O

``	O
I	B-ORG
Wonder	I-ORG
As	I-ORG
I	B-ORG
Wander	I-ORG
''	O

Jackson	B-PER
McDonald	I-PER
-	O
Career	O
FSO	O

The	O
``	O
British	B-PER
Invasion	I-PER
''	O
begins	O
.	O

Abraham	B-PER
H.	I-PER
Schenck	I-PER

Mezná	B-LOC
(	I-LOC
Pelhřimov	I-LOC
District	I-LOC
)	I-LOC

Prior	O
to	O
the	O
final	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
semi-final	O
where	O
artists	O
like	O
Nino	B-PER
Bravo	I-PER
had	O
been	O
eliminated	O
.	O

It	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
only	O
seven	O
known	O
manuscripts	O
in	O
this	O
style	O
,	O
all	O
originating	O
from	O
the	O
lower	B-LOC
Netherlands	I-LOC
.	O

Vikram	B-ORG
Sarabhai	I-ORG
Space	I-ORG
Centre	I-ORG

Whitefish	B-LOC
River	I-LOC
First	I-LOC
Nation	I-LOC

University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Veterinary	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Animal	I-ORG
Sciences	I-ORG
Pattoki	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Ravi	I-ORG
Campus	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Peterson	B-LOC
Township	I-LOC
,	O
Clay	B-LOC
County	I-LOC

'	O
''	O
Yellow-crested	B-LOC
cockatoo	I-LOC
''	O
'	O

Faculty	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Information	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
(	O
)	O
University	B-ORG
Džemal	I-ORG
Bijedić	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Mostar	I-ORG
was	O
founded	O
in	O
1997	O
.	O

**	O
109P	B-ORG
/	I-ORG
Swift-Tuttle	I-ORG
(	O
a.k.a	O
.	O

''	O
Trachelipus	B-LOC
planarius	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Budde-Lund	O
,	O
1885	O
)	O

''	O
A	B-ORG
World	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Our	I-ORG
Own	I-ORG
''	O
–	O
The	B-ORG
Seekers	I-ORG

The	B-ORG
Alternate	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Star	I-ORG
Trek	I-ORG
:	I-ORG
Deep	I-ORG
Space	I-ORG
Nine	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Bob	B-PER
Cohen	I-PER
,	O
also	O
a	O
reviewer	O
.	O

'	O
''	O
Cambridge	B-ORG
Winterhawks	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
(	O
MW	O
)	O

Y	B-ORG
Combinator	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
company	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

'	O
''	O
Cainta	B-ORG
''	O
'	O

November	O
20	O
:	O
The	B-ORG
King	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
Doctor	I-ORG
''	O

``	O
Nookie	B-ORG
''	O
/	O
``	O
Break	B-ORG
Stuff	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
Limp	B-ORG
Bizkit	I-ORG
)	O
–	O
2:35	O

He	O
asked	O
Sri	B-ORG
Ramakrishna	I-ORG
for	O
his	O
permission	O
to	O
renounce	O
worldly	O
life	O
.	O

''	O
Long	B-ORG
Way	I-ORG
Round	I-ORG
''	O

Edward	B-PER
G.	I-PER
Robinson	I-PER
,	O
Ida	B-PER
Lupino	I-PER
,	O
John	B-PER
Garfield	I-PER

``	O
God	B-ORG
Bless	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
USA	I-ORG
''	O
–	O
Lee	B-PER
Greenwood	I-PER

Ian	B-PER
Millar	I-PER
,	O
''athlete	O
''	O
,	O
1990	O

2000–2004	O
-	O
Boris	B-PER
Labar	I-PER

New	B-ORG
York	I-ORG
State	I-ORG
Route	I-ORG
192	I-ORG

the	O
BNSF	B-ORG
Railway	I-ORG
's	O
Salmon	B-ORG
Bay	I-ORG
Bridge	I-ORG
over	O
Salmon	B-LOC
Bay	I-LOC

'	O
''	O
In	B-ORG
the	I-ORG
Court	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Crimson	I-ORG
King	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
''	O

Anthony	B-PER
Robinson	I-PER
(	I-PER
novelist	I-PER
)	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1931	O
)	O

Romanian	B-ORG
Cup	I-ORG
:	O
2000	O
,	O
2001	O

Roman	B-LOC
Catholic	I-LOC
Territorial	I-LOC
Prelature	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Chota	I-LOC

Filming	O
began	O
on	O
March	O
18	O
,	O
2002	O
in	O
Arizona	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
moved	O
on	O
April	O
19	O
to	O
the	O
San	B-LOC
Francisco	I-LOC
Bay	I-LOC
Area	I-LOC
.	O

It	O
was	O
released	O
on	O
Merge	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG
on	O
March	O
11	O
,	O
1997	O
.	O

**	O
Franz	B-PER
Joseph	I-PER
I	I-PER
of	I-PER
Austria	I-PER
(	O
1848–1916	O
)	O

The	O
under	O
12s	O
and	O
under	O
14s	O
teams	O
were	O
established	O
with	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
National	B-ORG
Lottery	I-ORG
funding	O
.	O

*1997	O
:	O
Brown	B-ORG
Album	I-ORG
''	O

It	O
is	O
a	O
subsidiary	O
of	O
Ingram	B-ORG
Industries	I-ORG
.	O

Flashback	B-ORG
:	I-ORG
The	I-ORG
Quest	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
Identity	I-ORG
(	O
1992	O
)	O

``	O
Retailers	O
to	O
carry	O
his	O
work	O
include	O
Bergdorf	B-ORG
,	O
Saks	B-ORG
Fifth	I-ORG
Avenue	I-ORG
,	O
Bloomingdales	B-ORG
,	O
Henri	B-ORG
Bendel	I-ORG
,	O
Neiman-Marcus	B-ORG
,	O
and	O
Anthropologie	B-ORG
.	O

'	O
''	O
Rockland	B-ORG
Boulders	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

David	B-PER
Valesky	I-PER
(	O
identifies	O
as	O
an	O
``	O
Independent	B-PER
Democrat	I-PER
''	O
since	O
January	O
2011	O
)	O

'	O
''	O
High	B-ORG
five	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
is	O
a	O
gesture	O
.	O

Bob	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
Lake	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
Parry	I-LOC
Sound	I-LOC
District	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Ontario	I-LOC
)	I-LOC

Auk	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
''	O
121	O
''	O
'	O
(	O
3	O
)	O
:	O
847–864	O
.	O

'	O
''	O
Quetta	B-LOC
''	O
'	O

**	O
Air	B-ORG
Force	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Latvia	I-ORG

Pinball	B-ORG
Wizard	I-ORG
by	O
The	B-ORG
Who	I-ORG

Tsuneyuki	B-PER
Nakajima	I-PER
,	O
Kiyoshi	B-PER
Murota	I-PER
,	O
Tateo	B-PER
Ozaki	I-PER
,	O
Tsukasa	B-PER
Watanabe	I-PER
,	O
Hajime	B-PER
Meshiai	I-PER

'	O
''	O
Mauritius	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
-	O

He	O
released	O
his	O
first	O
solo	O
album	O
,	O
Lazarus	B-ORG
''	O
,	O
on	O
June	O
8	O
,	O
2010	O
.	O

Andrés	B-PER
de	I-PER
Olmos	I-PER

Tuesday	O
,	O
October	O
14	O
,	O
2003	O
at	O
Wrigley	B-ORG
Field	I-ORG
in	O
Chicago	B-LOC

Sears	B-ORG
(	O
66,320	O
sq	O
ft	O
)	O

'	O
''	O
Pronay	B-PER
Halder	I-PER
''	O
'	O

Felix	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Nabor	I-ORG
)	O
.	O

Those	O
teams	O
upset	O
higher	O
seeded	O
St.	B-ORG
John	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
and	O
Kansas	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
,	O
respectively	O
.	O

On	O
3	O
February	O
1958	O
,	O
the	O
ship	O
reported	O
to	O
Long	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
for	O
inactivation	O
.	O

Monahans	B-ORG
Sandhills	I-ORG
State	I-ORG
Park	I-ORG
near	O
Odessa	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Texas	I-LOC
.	O

PAW	B-ORG
Patrol	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2013–present	O
)	O

He	O
later	O
had	O
spells	O
at	O
Dundee	B-ORG
and	O
Partick	B-ORG
Thistle	I-ORG
before	O
retiring	O
in	O
1992	O
.	O

In	O
1924	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
building	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
Cyprus	B-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
was	O
completed	O
.	O

Chruściki	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Greater	I-LOC
Poland	I-LOC
Voivodeship	I-LOC

Rinnō-ji	B-ORG
at	O
Nikkō	B-ORG
,	O
Tochigi	B-LOC
Prefecture	I-LOC
,	O
Japan	B-LOC
.	O

During	O
the	O
Night	B-PER
of	I-PER
the	I-PER
Long	I-PER
Knives	I-PER
he	O
only	O
narrowly	O
missed	O
being	O
arrested	O
and	O
murdered	O
.	O

*8	O
August	O
-	O
André	B-PER
Jolivet	I-PER
,	O
composer	O
(	O
died	O
1974	O
)	O

''	O
The	B-PER
Big	I-PER
Breakfast	I-PER
''	O
(	O
1992–2002	O
)	O

He	O
won	O
his	O
first	O
victory	O
there	O
,	O
shared	O
with	O
Francesco	B-PER
Baracca	I-PER
on	O
23	O
August	O
1916	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
second	O
one	O
go	O
unconfirmed	O
.	O

Ellenborough	B-ORG
Park	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Weston-super-Mare	I-ORG

'	O
''	O
Darker	B-ORG
Than	I-ORG
Darkness	I-ORG
-Style	I-ORG
93-	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
''	O

Mahanoy	B-ORG
Area	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
District	I-ORG

*L'Envoi	O
(	O
Sarojini	B-PER
Naidu	I-PER
)	O
,	O
1935	O

Athletics	B-ORG
at	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
2003	I-ORG
Pan	I-ORG
American	I-ORG
Games	I-ORG
-	I-ORG
Women	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
heptathlon	I-ORG

Rafael	B-PER
Edri	I-PER
(	O
1988–90	O
)	O

Dave	B-PER
Audé	I-PER
(	O
13	O
)	O

Tony	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Beetles	I-ORG
''	O

''	O
Barghawata	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
–	O
Ilyâs	B-PER
ibn	I-PER
Sâlih	I-PER
(	O
792–842	O
)	O

The	B-LOC
Kingston	I-LOC
Trio	I-LOC
:	I-LOC
The	B-LOC
Stewart	I-LOC
Years	I-LOC
''	O

The	O
Mayor	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Pichilemu	I-ORG
is	O
elected	O
every	O
4	O
years	O
.	O

In	O
1919	O
her	O
family	O
moved	O
to	O
East	B-LOC
Cleveland	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Ohio	I-LOC
,	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
until	O
adulthood	O
.	O

Season	B-ORG
9	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
2013	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
:	O
Kevin	B-PER
Walker	I-PER

Southern	B-ORG
Railway	I-ORG
,	O
South	B-ORG
Central	I-ORG
Railway	I-ORG
,	O
South	B-ORG
Western	I-ORG
Railway	I-ORG
,	O
West	B-ORG
Central	I-ORG
Railway	I-ORG
and	O
North	B-ORG
Western	I-ORG
Railway	I-ORG
.	O

Jive	B-ORG
Bunny	I-ORG
:	I-ORG
The	I-ORG
Album	I-ORG
''	O

His	O
loan	O
was	O
extended	O
for	O
a	O
third	O
month	O
on	O
3	O
November	O
,	O
keeping	O
him	O
at	O
Huish	B-ORG
Park	I-ORG
until	O
11	O
December	O
.	O

Guy	B-PER
Debord	I-PER
(	O
Champot	O
)	O

Palouse	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Washington	I-LOC
–	O

Colegio	B-ORG
de	I-ORG
la	I-ORG
Preciosa	I-ORG
Sangre	I-ORG
de	I-ORG
Pichilemu	I-ORG
-	O
''CC.AA	O
.	O

Linn	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG
,	O
2014	O
.	O

Queen	B-ORG
Anne	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Caversham	I-ORG

The	O
funds	O
to	O
build	O
the	O
structure	O
were	O
provided	O
by	O
Andrew	B-PER
Carnegie	I-PER
.	O

Modena	B-LOC
Park	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Philadelphia	I-LOC

It	O
is	O
usually	O
associated	O
with	O
the	O
Pan-Green	B-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
and	O
supports	O
Taiwan	B-ORG
independence	I-ORG
.	O

Egerton	B-ORG
Grey	I-ORG
Country	I-ORG
House	I-ORG
Hotel	I-ORG
,	O
Barry	B-LOC

William	B-PER
Goetz	I-PER
,	O
producer	O
and	O
former	O
head	O
of	O
Universal	B-ORG
Studios	I-ORG

Mobb	B-ORG
Deep	I-ORG
-	O
Murda	B-ORG
Muzik	I-ORG
''	O
===	O

San	B-ORG
Diego	I-ORG
Charger	I-ORG
Girls	I-ORG

Annette	B-PER
Karmiloff-Smith	I-PER
,	O
professor	O

Jennings	B-PER
Randolph	I-PER
–	O
1	O
(	O
0.03	O
%	O
)	O

Oostsanen	B-PER
,	I-PER
Jacob	I-PER
Corneliszoon	I-PER
van	I-PER
(	O
Oostzaan	B-LOC
,	O
1472	O
–	O
Amsterdam	B-LOC
,	O
1533	O
)	O
,	O
5	O
works	O

She	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Borås	B-LOC
.	O

He	O
replaces	O
Giani	B-PER
Gurbachan	I-PER
Singh	I-PER
.	O

:	O
West	B-ORG
Limerick	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
UK	I-ORG
Parliament	I-ORG
constituency	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

'	O
''	O
Alexis	B-ORG
Gordon	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
6–3	O
6–3	O

Liège–Bastogne–Liège]]	O
(	O
Alejandro	B-PER
Valverde	I-PER
)	O

She	O
died	O
on	O
November	O
7	O
,	O
1946	O
in	O
Los	B-LOC
Angeles	I-LOC
.	O

He	O
is	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
manager	O
Josef	B-PER
Hickersberger	I-PER
.	O

He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Oriskany	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
New	I-LOC
York	I-LOC
,	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
Welsh	B-LOC
immigrants	O
.	O

José	B-PER
Luis	I-PER
Calderón	I-PER

When	O
he	O
joined	O
the	O
Canadian	B-ORG
Expeditionary	I-ORG
Force	I-ORG
on	O
17	O
May	O
1915	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
working	O
as	O
a	O
banker	O
.	O

:	O
:	O
:	O
:	O
:	O
:	O
:	O
:	O
:	O
:	O
:	O
:C.	O
Prince	B-PER
Moritz	I-PER
of	I-PER
Saxe-Altenburg	I-PER
,	O
1829–1907	O
,	O
had	O
1	O
son	O
;	O

His	O
brother-in-law	O
was	O
Barend	B-PER
Joseph	I-PER
Stokvis	I-PER
.	O

'	O
''	O
''	O
is	O
a	O
book	O
by	O
Barbara	B-PER
Robinson	I-PER
.	O

'	O
''	O
Özge	B-PER
Bayrak	I-PER
''	O
'	O
21-18	O
,	O
21-14	O

Rupert	B-PER
,	I-PER
Duke	I-PER
of	I-PER
Cumberland	I-PER
(	O
1619–1682	O
)	O
;	O
had	O
two	O
illegitimate	O
children	O

Richard	B-PER
Harris	I-PER
,	O
James	B-PER
Gammon	I-PER
,	O
Dub	B-PER
Taylor	I-PER

389th	B-ORG
Fighter	I-ORG
Squadron	I-ORG

David	B-ORG
Byrne	I-ORG
sued	O
the	O
band	O
,	O
saying	O
their	O
name	O
and	O
presentation	O
was	O
too	O
evocative	O
of	O
Talking	B-ORG
Heads	I-ORG
,	O
and	O
put	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
those	O
plans	O
.	O

**	O
(	O
)	O
Diabetes	B-ORG
with	I-ORG
neurological	I-ORG
manifestations	I-ORG

Prominence	B-LOC
and	I-LOC
Demise	I-LOC
(	O
2007	O
)	O

Mountain	B-ORG
View–Winchester	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
VTA	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Damian	B-PER
Cronin	I-PER
,	O
3	O
.	O

Pete	B-PER
Varney	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1949	O
)	O
,	O
Major	B-ORG
League	I-ORG
Baseball	I-ORG
player	O

:	O
Apulia	B-LOC
and	O
Campania	B-LOC
''	O

Nièvre	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
2nd	I-LOC
constituency	I-LOC

``	O
I	B-ORG
Love	I-ORG
Living	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
City	I-ORG
''	O
by	O
Fear	B-ORG

MacQueen	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
bustard	I-LOC
,	O
(	O
''Chlamydotis	O
macqueenii	O
''	O
)	O

He	O
died	O
at	O
95	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
funeral	O
was	O
held	O
in	O
Les	B-ORG
Invalides	I-ORG
.	O

The	B-ORG
Eastbourne	I-ORG
Academy	I-ORG
,	O
Eastbourne	B-LOC

Nocturnes	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
Field	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

R.	B-ORG
Budi	I-ORG
Hartono	I-ORG
,	O
CEO	O
of	O
Djarum	B-ORG
Cigarettes	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG

Southwest	B-ORG
Conference’s	I-ORG
Most	O
Valuable	O
Player	O

*The	O
nearby	O
Sacra	B-ORG
di	I-ORG
San	I-ORG
Michele	I-ORG
''	O
.	O

Old	B-ORG
Sarum	I-ORG
,	O
Salisbury	B-ORG
Cathedral	I-ORG

'	O
''	O
Denis	B-PER
Zivkovic	I-PER
''	O
'	O

In	O
1808	O
he	O
became	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	B-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Netherlands	I-ORG
.	O

'	O
''	O
Nora	B-PER
Ephron	I-PER
''	O
'	O

Dave	B-PER
Casper	I-PER
,	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Notre	I-ORG
Dame	I-ORG

Released	O
independently	O
in	O
Cleveland	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
Ohio	I-ORG
in	O
1995	O
.	O

Tuesday	O
,	O
October	O
20	O
,	O
2009	O
at	O
Munhak	B-ORG
Baseball	I-ORG
Stadium	I-ORG
in	O
Incheon	B-LOC

Four	B-ORG
Sephardic	I-ORG
Synagogues	I-ORG

In	O
2002	O
,	O
the	O
song	O
was	O
remastered	O
for	O
release	O
on	O
The	B-ORG
Best	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Siouxsie	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Banshees	I-ORG
''	O
.	O

He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Mulhouse	B-LOC
,	O
Haut-Rhin	B-LOC
,	O
Alsace	B-LOC
.	O

Institute	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Business	I-ORG
Studies	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Research	I-ORG

Cardamine	B-LOC
''	O
(	O
bittercress	B-LOC
)	O

Kim	B-PER
Sang-woo	I-PER
(	I-PER
referee	I-PER
)	I-PER

Estadio	B-ORG
Atilio	I-ORG
Paiva	I-ORG
Olivera	I-ORG
,	O
Rivera	B-LOC
,	O
Uruguay	B-LOC

``	O
No	B-ORG
Leaf	I-ORG
Clover	I-ORG
''	O

Ariel	B-PER
Sharon	I-PER
(	O
1998-1999	O
)	O

Visalia	B-LOC
(	O
Fresno	B-LOC
)	O
–	O
KMPH-TV	B-ORG
26	O

After	O
its	O
July	O
8	O
,	O
2005	O
debut	O
on	O
MuchMusic	B-ORG
's	O
Countdown	B-ORG
''	O
,	O
it	O
reached	O
number	O
one	O
for	O
the	O
week	O
of	O
October	O
8	O
,	O
2005	O
.	O

Equipped	O
Bench	B-ORG
Press	I-ORG
-	O
1201	O
lbs	O

'	O
''	O
Rhonda	B-PER
Rajsich	I-PER
''	O
'1-11	O
,	O
11-8	O
,	O
11-3	O
,	O
2-11	O
,	O
11-7	O

'	O
''	O
–	O
Justus	B-ORG
Ferdinand	I-ORG
Poggenburg	I-ORG
I	I-ORG
(	O
1840–1893	O
)	O

Manhattan	B-ORG
Spotlight	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1949–1951	O
)	O

'	O
''	O
Hummel	B-ORG
Ultracruiser	I-ORG
Plus	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

He	O
served	O
on	O
the	O
faculty	O
of	O
the	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Michigan	I-ORG
in	O
1954-69	O
,	O
before	O
moving	O
to	O
Harvard	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
as	O
a	O
full	O
professor	O
.	O

In	O
May	O
2013	O
,	O
the	O
headquarters	O
moved	O
from	O
Datong	B-LOC
District	I-LOC
,	O
Taipei	B-LOC
to	O
Neihu	B-LOC
District	I-LOC
,	O
Taipei	B-LOC
.	O

Prnjavor	B-LOC
,	O
population	O
38,399	O

Haji	B-ORG
Husein	I-ORG
Alireza	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Co.	I-ORG
Ltd	I-ORG
.	I-ORG

****	O
Pondichéry	B-LOC
(	O
1765–1954	O
)	O

The	O
final	O
was	O
played	O
at	O
Santiago	B-ORG
Bernabéu	I-ORG
Stadium	I-ORG
in	O
Madrid	B-LOC
on	O
24	O
June	O
1995	O
.	O

Kiss	B-ORG
–	O
Destroyer	B-ORG
''	O

List	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
countries	I-ORG
by	I-ORG
number	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
troops	I-ORG

1929–30	B-ORG
Birmingham	I-ORG
F.C.	I-ORG
season	I-ORG

``	O
Ticket	B-ORG
to	I-ORG
Ride	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
previously	O
unissued	O
single	O
mix	O
)	O

Stepmom	B-ORG
was	O
ranked	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
genre	O
of	O
mother	O
.	O

It	O
is	O
from	O
the	O
West	B-LOC
Rapti	I-LOC
River	I-LOC
.	O

In	O
1940	O
,	O
she	O
joined	O
the	O
Peace	B-ORG
Pledge	I-ORG
Union	I-ORG
.	O

On	O
11	O
March	O
2002	O
,	O
the	O
Supreme	B-ORG
Court	I-ORG
agreed	O
,	O
by	O
six	O
votes	O
to	O
one	O
.	O

''	O
Chrysopsyche	B-LOC
pauliani	I-LOC
''	O
Viette	O
,	O
1962	O

Sealock	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
Family	I-ORG
name	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Lidlington	B-ORG
railway	I-ORG
station	I-ORG

Clare	B-ORG
College	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Cambridge	I-ORG

Almost	O
two	O
thirds	O
of	O
the	O
entire	O
population	O
of	O
Catania	B-LOC
were	O
killed	O
.	O

The	O
competition	O
was	O
held	O
in	O
Łódź	B-LOC
,	O
Poland	B-LOC
and	O
took	O
place	O
May	O
9–18	O
,	O
1958	O
.	O

The	O
'	O
''	O
United	B-ORG
Provinces	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
River	I-ORG
Plate	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
supersedes	O
the	O
United	B-ORG
Provinces	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
South	I-ORG
America	I-ORG
.	O

Linda	B-PER
Runbeck	I-PER
,	O
Republican	B-ORG
Party	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Minnesota	I-ORG
member	O
of	O
the	O
Minnesota	B-ORG
House	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Representatives	I-ORG
;	O
former	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
Minnesota	B-ORG
Senate	I-ORG

World	B-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Reformed	I-ORG
Churches	I-ORG

``	O
The	O
scene	O
was	O
submitted	O
to	O
the	O
British	B-ORG
Board	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Film	I-ORG
Classification	I-ORG
for	O
evaluation	O
.	O

He	O
stayed	O
there	O
for	O
two	O
seasons	O
,	O
playing	O
in	O
the	O
French	B-ORG
Pro	I-ORG
A	I-ORG
and	O
Eurocup	B-ORG
.	O

He	O
then	O
moved	O
to	O
the	O
ECHL	B-ORG
and	O
played	O
four	O
more	O
seasons	O
before	O
retiring	O
in	O
1995	O
.	O

He	O
goes	O
to	O
Italy	B-LOC
.	O

Geschwaderkommodore	B-ORG
''	O
of	O
Kampfgeschwader	B-ORG
100	I-ORG

Qualified	O
for	O
1973-74	B-ORG
UEFA	I-ORG
Cup	I-ORG
.	O

Oxford	B-LOC
-	O
3.1	O
%	O

2000	O
Songs	B-ORG
in	I-ORG
Red	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Gray	I-ORG
''	O
-	O
Suzanne	B-PER
Vega	I-PER

Mick	B-PER
Barry	I-PER
(	I-PER
rugby	I-PER
union	I-PER
)	I-PER

:	O
Voiced	O
by	O
:	O
Megumi	B-PER
Hayashibara	I-PER

Great	B-LOC
grey	I-LOC
shrike	I-LOC
,	O
''Lanius	O
excubitor	O
''	O
A	O

Talia	B-PER
Shire	I-PER
as	O
Constanzia	B-PER
``	I-PER
Connie	I-PER
''	I-PER
Corleone	I-PER

*Distinguished	O
Professor	O
of	O
Stony	B-ORG
Brook	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
(	O
2002	O
)	O

-	O
Adam	B-PER
Grant	I-PER
,	O
The	B-ORG
New	I-ORG
York	I-ORG
Times	I-ORG
''	O
bestselling	O
author	O
of	O
''Give	O
and	O
Take	O
''	O

:	O
:	O
:	O
DEA1B	O
Kleve	B-LOC

Grande	B-ORG
Hotel	I-ORG
da	I-ORG
Póvoa	I-ORG

*Countess	O
Christiane	B-PER
of	I-PER
Schleswig-Holstein	I-PER
(	O
15	O
July	O
1626	O
–	O
6	O
May	O
1670	O
)	O
;	O
married	O
Hannibal	B-PER
Sehested	I-PER

Greater	B-LOC
London	I-LOC
,	O
which	O
is	O
divided	O
into	O
32	O
London	B-LOC
boroughs	I-LOC
and	O
the	O
City	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
London	I-LOC

College	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Staten	I-ORG
Island	I-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
International	I-ORG
Studies	I-ORG

''	O
Dorstenia	B-LOC
peltata	I-LOC
''	O

San	B-LOC
Vicente	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Moravia	I-LOC

''	O
Pinus	B-LOC
hwangshanensis	I-LOC
''	O

At	B-ORG
the	I-ORG
Organ	I-ORG

Fortycoats]]	O
''	O
)	O
,	O
Tom	B-PER
McGurk	I-PER

British	B-ORG
Peoples	I-ORG
Party	I-ORG
(	O
2005–2013	O
)	O

Hengoed	B-ORG
railway	I-ORG
station	I-ORG

King	B-ORG
George	I-ORG
III	I-ORG
had	O
issued	O
a	O
demand	O
for	O
its	O
retraction	O
.	O

She	O
appears	O
in	O
other	O
songs	O
on	O
their	O
2007	O
artist	O
album	O
Gabriel	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Dresden	I-ORG
''	O
.	O

performances	O
by	O
such	O
acts	O
as	O
The	B-ORG
Doors	I-ORG
,	O
Alice	B-PER
Cooper	I-PER
,	O
Pink	B-ORG
Floyd	I-ORG
,	O
Love	B-ORG
,	O
The	B-ORG
Mothers	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Invention	I-ORG
,	O
The	B-ORG
Seeds	I-ORG
,	O
Buffalo	B-ORG
Springfield	I-ORG
and	O
others	O
.	O

'	O
''	O
Elgin	B-LOC
:	O
'	O
''	O
at	O
Dr	B-ORG
Gray	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
Hospital	I-ORG
.	O

Emmanuel	B-PER
Marie	I-PER
Louis	I-PER
de	I-PER
Noailles	I-PER

Thaworn	B-PER
Wiratchant	I-PER
(	O
7	O
)	O

She	O
was	O
reconstructed	O
at	O
the	O
Imperial	B-ORG
Dockyard	I-ORG
in	O
Kiel	B-LOC
that	O
year	O
.	O

*7	O
Apr	O
-	O
Bing	B-PER
Crosby	I-PER

Christian	B-PER
Müller	I-PER
(	I-PER
footballer	I-PER
,	I-PER
born	I-PER
1984	I-PER
)	I-PER

Animalia	B-PER
(	I-PER
TV	I-PER
series	I-PER
)	I-PER

Vladimir	B-PER
Sukhomlinov	I-PER
11	O
March	O
1909	O
–	O
13	O
June	O
1915	O

North	B-LOC
Plains	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Oregon	I-LOC

Dan	B-PER
Pastorini	I-PER
(	O
1–1	O
)	O

Harold	B-PER
Faltermeyer	I-PER
—	O
``	O
Axel	B-ORG
F	I-ORG
''	O

``	O
The	B-ORG
Canadian	I-ORG
Geographer	I-ORG
''	O
38	O
,	O
265-70	O
.	O

Dedeler	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Gülnar	I-LOC

Sean	B-PER
Paul	I-PER
featuring	O
Alexis	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER

Solvay	B-PER
,	I-PER
E	I-PER
.	I-PER
(	O
1906	O
)	O
.	O

It	O
was	O
built	O
and	O
is	O
owned	O
by	O
MTR	B-ORG
Corporation	I-ORG
(	O
MTRC	O
)	O
in	O
conjunction	O
with	O
the	O
opening	O
of	O
Tsing	B-ORG
Yi	I-ORG
Station	I-ORG
.	O

NCAA	B-ORG
on	I-ORG
C	I-ORG
/	I-ORG
S9	I-ORG
(	O
also	O
broadcast	O
on	O
ABS-CBN	B-ORG
Sports	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Action	I-ORG
and	O
BTV	B-ORG
)	O
(	O
produced	O
by	O
ABS-CBN	B-LOC
Sports	I-LOC
and	O
Solar	B-ORG
Sports	I-ORG
)	O

Jane	B-ORG
the	I-ORG
Virgin	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2016	O
)	O

:	O
Luke	B-PER
Williams	I-PER
(	O
vs	O
Barnsley	B-ORG
18	O
December	O
2009	O
)	O

Stopes	B-PER
,	I-PER
Charlotte	I-PER
Carmichael	I-PER
.	O

Myrne	B-LOC
-	O
former	O
name	O
:	O
Telache	O
(	O
Telacze	O
)	O

Director	O
of	O
La	B-ORG
2	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Spain	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Kensington	B-LOC
and	O
died	O
in	O
Bushey	B-ORG
Hall	I-ORG
,	O
Hertfordshire	B-LOC
.	O

Alfred	B-PER
Runge	I-PER
(	O
1881–1946	O
)	O

He	O
died	O
in	O
Brooklyn	B-LOC
,	O
New	B-LOC
York	I-LOC
on	O
August	O
2	O
,	O
1861	O
.	O

United	B-ORG
States	I-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Forces	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
Europe	I-ORG
,	O
10	O
September	O
1962	O

His	O
appearance	O
resembles	O
Rodimus	B-ORG
Prime	I-ORG
.	O

Andrew	B-ORG
J.	I-ORG
Hamilton	I-ORG
(	O
ID	O
)	O

Cannon	B-PER
and	I-PER
Ball	I-PER

Flavio	B-PER
Cipolla	I-PER
/	O
Paolo	B-PER
Lorenzi	I-PER

He	O
started	O
writing	O
short	O
stories	O
for	O
Black	B-ORG
Mask	I-ORG
''	O
in	O
1932	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Los	B-LOC
Angeles	I-LOC
area	O
.	O

Tim	B-PER
Matthys	I-PER
(	O
Zulte	B-ORG
Waregem	I-ORG
)	O

'	O
''	O
Betty	B-PER
Stöve	I-PER
''	O
'	O
/	O
'	O
''	O
Wendy	B-PER
Turnbull	I-PER
''	O
'	O
defeated	O
Françoise	B-PER
Dürr	I-PER
/	O
Virginia	B-PER
Wade	I-PER
,	O
3–6	O
,	O
7–5	O
,	O
6–4	O

Middle	B-ORG
Longhua	I-ORG
Road	I-ORG
Station	I-ORG

``	O
Evidence	O
''	O
(	O
7	O
''	O
)	O
–	O
with	O
John	B-PER
Foxx	I-PER
and	O
The	O
Maths	O
–	O
Captured	O
Tracks	O
(	O
September	O
2012	O
)	O

Con	B-PER
Lehane	I-PER
(	I-PER
Irish	I-PER
republican	I-PER
)	I-PER

Grey	B-LOC
peacock-pheasant	I-LOC
(	O
''P	O
.	O

Henry	B-ORG
Cocks	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

She	O
has	O
served	O
as	O
the	O
Chair	O
of	O
the	O
Alabama	B-ORG
Republican	I-ORG
Party	I-ORG
since	O
February	O
2015	O
.	O

Dot	B-PER
Branning	I-PER
-	O
June	B-PER
Brown	I-PER

*An	O
instrumental	O
arrangement	O
by	O
guitarist	O
Davy	B-ORG
Graham	I-ORG
was	O
included	O
in	O
his	O
reissue	O
1978	O
album	O
The	B-ORG
Complete	I-ORG
Guitarist	I-ORG
in	O
1999	O

from	O
the	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Chicago	I-ORG
Law	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
.	O

``	O
Yo	B-ORG
!	I-ORG
Bum	I-ORG
Rush	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Show	I-ORG
''	O
by	O
Public	B-ORG
Enemy	I-ORG

''	O
'	O
''	O
Teacher	B-PER
's	I-PER
Pet	I-PER
''	O
'	O
''	O

He	O
fought	O
Nik	B-PER
Lentz	I-PER
,	O
losing	O
via	O
unanimous	O
decision	O
after	O
being	O
out	O
wrestled	O
for	O
all	O
three	O
rounds	O
.	O

She	O
grew	O
up	O
in	O
Pasadena	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
California	I-LOC
.	O

He	O
also	O
spent	O
time	O
representing	O
the	O
Netherlands	B-LOC
in	O
the	O
2000	B-ORG
Olympics	I-ORG
.	O

Clifton	B-ORG
Hall	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
15th-century	O
Pele	B-ORG
tower	I-ORG
.	O

Murder	B-PER
of	I-PER
Annie	I-PER
Le	I-PER

Hemprich	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
hornbill	I-LOC
,	O
'	O
''	O
'	O

Kevin	B-PER
Kopelow	I-PER
and	I-PER
Heath	I-PER
Seifert	I-PER

'	O
''	O
√	O
Pierce	B-PER
Butler	I-PER
''	O
'	O
(	O
Anti-Administration	O
)	O

Night	B-ORG
''	O
(	O
2012	O
)	O

Hoërskool	B-ORG
Jim	I-ORG
Fouché	I-ORG
,	O
Bloemfontein	B-LOC

Recording	B-ORG
sessions	I-ORG
took	O
place	O
at	O
Radio	B-LOC
Recorders	I-LOC
in	O
Hollywood	B-LOC
on	O
August	O
30	O
and	O
September	O
22	O
,	O
1962	O
.	O

S-Line	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
Norfolk	I-ORG
Southern	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Napalm	B-ORG
Death	I-ORG
-	O
You	B-LOC
Suffer	I-LOC

Roman	B-LOC
Catholic	I-LOC
Diocese	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Ponce	I-LOC
(	O
erected	O
in	O
1924	O
)	O

He	O
has	O
previously	O
played	O
for	O
St.	B-ORG
George	I-ORG
Illawarra	I-ORG
Dragons	I-ORG
,	O
Parramatta	B-ORG
Eels	I-ORG
,	O
South	B-ORG
Sydney	I-ORG
Rabbitohs	I-ORG
and	O
Rugby	B-ORG
Union	I-ORG
for	O
the	O
NSW	B-ORG
Waratahs	I-ORG
.	O

Dale	B-PER
Nichols	I-PER
-	O
Artist	O

''	O
I	B-ORG
Think	I-ORG
We	I-ORG
're	I-ORG
Alone	I-ORG
Now	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1967	O
)	O

Among	O
the	O
performers	O
were	O
Max	B-ORG
Rosenbloom	I-ORG
,	O
Buddy	B-PER
Hackett	I-PER
,	O
Polly	B-PER
Bergen	I-PER
,	O
Alan	B-PER
King	I-PER
,	O
Billy	B-PER
Barty	I-PER
,	O
Don	B-PER
Rickles	I-PER
and	O
Jackie	B-PER
Gleason	I-PER
.	O

By	O
1900	O
Germans	O
lived	O
in	O
more	O
dispersed	O
neighborhoods	O
,	O
including	O
the	O
Near	B-ORG
North	I-ORG
Side	I-ORG
neighborhood	O
,	O
Florence	B-LOC
and	O
South	B-ORG
Omaha	I-ORG
.	O

The	O
recording	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
during	O
a	O
1997	O
concert	O
performance	O
in	O
Green	B-LOC
Bay	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Wisconsin	I-LOC
,	O
barely	O
made	O
it	O
onto	O
the	O
final	O
album	O
.	O

-	O
Census	B-LOC
town	I-LOC
,	O
O.G	O
.	O

It	O
was	O
praised	O
by	O
The	B-ORG
A.V.	I-ORG
Club	I-ORG
''	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
``	O
resounding	O
success	O
in	O
that	O
regard	O
:	O
It	O
's	O
eclectic	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
self-consciously	O
so	O
.	O

Anthony	B-PER
A.	I-PER
Hoekema	I-PER

He	O
was	O
the	O
eldest	O
son	O
of	O
George	B-PER
Hunter	I-PER
,	O
the	O
first	O
Mayor	B-PER
of	I-PER
Wellington	I-PER
.	O

He	O
graduated	O
from	O
the	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
London	I-ORG
.	O

Richard	B-PER
Ingrams	I-PER
(	O
1939-	O
)	O
,	O
journalist	O

He	O
was	O
invited	O
to	O
residency	O
programs	O
in	O
Vermont	B-LOC
in	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
America	I-LOC
in	O
1995	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
Monash	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
in	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
,	O
Australia	B-LOC
,	O
both	O
in	O
2006	O
and	O
in	O
2010	O
.	O

But	O
embassies	O
were	O
closing	O
their	O
doors	O
all	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
countries	O
,	O
including	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
,	O
were	O
closing	O
their	O
borders	O
.	O

15th	B-ORG
Lux	I-ORG
Style	I-ORG
Awards	I-ORG

James	B-PER
Hanley	I-PER
:	O
Novelist	O
and	O
playwright	O

São	B-LOC
João	I-LOC
de	I-LOC
Iracema	I-LOC
:	O
1,780	O

She	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Akaroa	B-LOC
,	O
North	B-ORG
Canterbury	I-ORG
,	O
New	B-LOC
Zealand	I-LOC
in	O
1884	O
.	O

Co-produced	O
with	O
TT	B-ORG
Fusion	I-ORG

Political	B-ORG
parties	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
Niue	I-ORG

James	B-PER
Fallows	I-PER
,	O
journalist	O
for	O
The	B-ORG
Atlantic	I-ORG
Monthly	I-ORG
''	O

Lloyd	B-PER
Zucker	I-PER
(	O
51	O
)	O

Sloan	B-ORG
,	O
``	O
If	B-ORG
It	I-ORG
Feels	I-ORG
Good	I-ORG
Do	I-ORG
It	I-ORG
''	O

Black-and-chestnut	B-LOC
eagle	I-LOC
,	O
''S	O
.	O

:	O
JR	B-ORG
West	I-ORG
Tokaido	B-ORG
Line	I-ORG
(	O
JR	B-ORG
Kobe	I-ORG
Line	I-ORG
)	O

Miles	O
wrote	O
several	O
papers	O
that	O
were	O
published	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	B-ORG
Geographical	I-ORG
Society	I-ORG
.	O

Jabłońskie	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Warmian-Masurian	I-LOC
Voivodeship	I-LOC

Then	O
,	O
in	O
2012	O
,	O
New	B-LOC
Hampshire	I-LOC
re-applied	O
after	O
having	O
rescinded	O
as	O
recently	O
as	O
2010	O
.	O

Cielętniki	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Silesian	I-LOC
Voivodeship	I-LOC

Royal	B-ORG
Flying	I-ORG
Corps	I-ORG
,	O
Royal	B-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Force	I-ORG
,	O
South	B-ORG
African	I-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Force	I-ORG

Sam	B-PER
Willaman	I-PER
,	O
head	O
coach	O
,	O
fourth	O
year	O

His	O
guest	O
was	O
professor	O
Peter	B-PER
Ward	I-PER
.	O

Hafez	B-PER
al-Assad	I-PER
first	O
commissioned	O
the	O
plans	O
for	O
the	O
building	O
in	O
1979	O
.	O

Diego	B-PER
del	I-PER
Gastor	I-PER

'	O
''	O
Sergio	B-PER
Casal	I-PER
Emilio	B-PER
Sánchez	I-PER
''	O
'	O
7–6	O
,	O
6–3	O

Paolo	B-PER
Panelli	I-PER
-	O
Photographer	O

'	O
''	O
2009	O
National	B-ORG
Board	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Review	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Motion	I-ORG
Pictures	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

Sierra	B-ORG
Leone	I-ORG
national	I-ORG
football	I-ORG
team	I-ORG
-	O
''the	O
Leone	B-ORG
Stars	I-ORG
''	O

Well	O
received	O
,	O
the	O
work	O
was	O
staged	O
the	O
following	O
year	O
at	O
the	O
Opéra	B-ORG
de	I-ORG
Monte-Carlo	I-ORG
.	O

Artists	O
on	O
the	O
label	O
included	O
Gilbert	B-PER
O'Sullivan	I-PER
,	O
Lynsey	B-PER
de	I-PER
Paul	I-PER
,	O
and	O
Dave	B-PER
Edmunds	I-PER
.	O

John	B-PER
Rutter	I-PER
-	O
``	O
I	B-ORG
will	I-ORG
sing	I-ORG
with	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
spirit	I-ORG
''	O

)	O
(	O
King	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
Birthday	I-ORG
Honours	I-ORG
List	I-ORG
1947	O
)	O

Turkish	B-ORG
Super	I-ORG
Cup	I-ORG
(	O
1	O
)	O
:	O
2010	B-ORG

Others	O
who	O
had	O
auditioned	O
for	O
the	O
part	O
included	O
Raymond	B-PER
Burr	I-PER
,	O
Richard	B-PER
Boone	I-PER
,	O
Denver	B-PER
Pyle	I-PER
,	O
and	O
William	B-PER
Conrad	I-PER
.	O

Charles	B-PER
D.	I-PER
Martin	I-PER
:	O
341,712	O

'	O
''	O
Toto	B-ORG
Cup	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Leumit	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
(	O
1	O
)	O
'	O
''	O

'	O
''	O
Harry	B-PER
Sohal	I-PER
''	O
'	O
(	O
1946-1994	O
)	O

Gene	B-PER
Autry	I-PER
as	O
Himself	O

Spadikam	B-PER
George	I-PER
..	O
Kaloorkadan	O
Kuttappayi	O

Princess	B-PER
Mary	I-PER
''Agnes	I-PER
''	I-PER
of	I-PER
Hohenlohe-Langenburg	I-PER
;	O
married	O
Konstantin	B-PER
,	I-PER
Hereditary	I-PER
Prince	I-PER
of	I-PER
Löwenstein-Wertheim-Rosenberg	I-PER

Arthur	B-PER
Hoffmann	I-PER
(	I-PER
resistance	I-PER
fighter	I-PER
)	I-PER

La	B-LOC
Chapelle-en-Lafaye	I-LOC
(	O
42050	O
)	O

Official	O
site	O
Democratic	B-ORG
Political	I-ORG
Turning	I-ORG
Point	I-ORG

Ai	B-ORG
n't	I-ORG
No	I-ORG
'H	I-ORG
'	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
Ripcordz	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Dork-Face	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1992	O
)	O

He	O
is	O
currently	O
serving	O
two	O
life	O
sentences	O
at	O
United	B-ORG
States	I-ORG
Penitentiary	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Tucson	I-ORG
.	O

Søren	B-PER
Kierkegaard	I-PER
,	O
Martin	B-PER
Heidegger	I-PER
,	O
Jean-Paul	B-PER
Sartre	I-PER
,	O
Simone	B-PER
de	I-PER
Beauvoir	I-PER
,	O
Albert	B-PER
Camus	I-PER
,	O
Hannah	B-PER
Arendt	I-PER
,	O
Hans	B-PER
Jonas	I-PER
,	O
Karl	B-PER
Löwith	I-PER
,	O
Herbert	B-PER
Marcuse	I-PER
,	O
Claude	B-PER
Lévi-Strauss	I-PER
,	O
Martin	B-PER
Buber	I-PER
,	O
Edmund	B-PER
Husserl	I-PER
.	O

Lockheed	B-ORG
Martin	I-ORG
and	O
TRW	B-ORG
)	O
.	O

Montreal	B-ORG
Bleu	I-ORG
Blanc	I-ORG
Rouge	I-ORG

Ferromagnetic	B-ORG
materials	O
can	O
be	O
magnetized	O
in	O
the	O
following	O
ways	O
:	O

:	O
Examples	O
may	O
include	O
``	O
Georgallis	B-ORG
''	O
and	O
``	O
Kanellis	B-PER
''	O
among	O
many	O
others	O
.	O

Noël	B-PER
Coward	I-PER
composed	O
a	O
song	O
which	O
was	O
titled	O
as	O
``	O
A	O
Room	O
with	O
a	O
View	O
''	O
in	O
1928	O
.	O

Adelaide	B-PER
of	I-PER
Savoy	I-PER
,	I-PER
Duchess	I-PER
of	I-PER
Swabia	I-PER

Houston	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
Texas	I-ORG
-	O
19,290	O
(	O
1	O
%	O
)	O
.	O

''Bigfoot	O
''	O
at	O
The	B-ORG
Asylum	I-ORG

County	B-LOC
Cork	I-LOC
,	O
Ireland	B-LOC
,	O
1920	O
.	O

''	O
Euphorbia	B-LOC
tannensis	I-LOC
''	O
Spreng	B-ORG
.	I-ORG
1807	O
(	O
s	O
)	O

Insects	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
album	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

**	O
Winner	O
:	O
Ju	B-PER
Wenjun	I-PER

Orlovac]].Ž3093	O
to	O
Gornja	B-LOC
Kovačica	I-LOC
and	O
Velika	B-LOC
Barna.Ž3094	I-LOC
to	O
Grubišno	B-LOC
Polje	I-LOC
and	O
Ivanovo	B-LOC
Selo	I-LOC
.	O

:	O
From	O
Gafsa	B-LOC
to	O
Medenine	B-LOC

Smokey	B-PER
Robinson	I-PER
(	O
2001	O
)	O

Zagórze	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Wieruszów	I-LOC
County	I-LOC

Kh.	B-PER
Khasmammedov	I-PER
–	O
State	B-ORG
Minister	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Internal	I-ORG
Affairs	I-ORG

He	O
is	O
incarcerated	O
in	O
Stateville	B-ORG
Correctional	I-ORG
Center	I-ORG
near	O
Joliet	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Illinois	I-LOC
.	O

Barbus	B-LOC
humeralis	I-LOC
''	O
Boulenger	B-PER
,	O
1902	O

Erwin	B-PER
Tulfo	I-PER
(	O
1995–2005	O
)	O
(	O
moved	O
to	O
RPN	B-ORG
2005–2008	O
;	O
TV5	B-ORG
2010–present	O
)	O

''	O
Whose	B-ORG
Life	I-ORG
is	I-ORG
it	I-ORG
Anyway	I-ORG
?	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1980	O
)	O

Carl	B-PER
Bell	I-PER
(	I-PER
physician	I-PER
)	I-PER

The	O
distance	O
to	O
Belo	B-LOC
Horizonte	I-LOC
is	O
557	O
km	O
.	O

Contrary	O
to	O
popular	O
belief	O
,	O
the	O
writer	O
and	O
director	O
Richard	B-PER
Kelly	I-PER
denied	O
referencing	O
'Harvey	O
'	O
.	O

'	O
''	O
With	O
Preston	B-PER
Love	I-PER
''	O
'	O

Çavuşlar	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Kızılcahamam	I-LOC

He	O
first	O
worked	O
as	O
a	O
teacher	O
at	O
Jesuit	B-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
in	O
Tampa	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Florida	I-LOC
from	O
1940	O
until	O
1943	O
.	O

'	O
''	O
Ankang	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
:	O
Xi'an–Ankang	B-ORG
Railway	I-ORG
,	O
Yangpingguan–Ankang	B-ORG
Railway	I-ORG

The	O
population	O
was	O
3,659	O
at	O
the	O
2010	B-ORG
U.S.	I-ORG
Census	I-ORG
.	O

Institute	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Space	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
IST	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Mahabharat	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
2013	I-ORG
TV	I-ORG
series	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
''	O

Arthur	B-PER
Bernardes	I-PER
(	O
2016-	O
)	O

*1986	O
-	O
Santa	B-LOC
Clara	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
California	I-LOC

'	O
''	O
Australian	B-ORG
Baseball	I-ORG
League	I-ORG
:	O
'	O
''	O
Sydney	B-ORG
Blue	I-ORG
Sox	I-ORG

Pell	B-LOC
City	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Alabama	I-LOC
$	O
19,935	O

Warren	B-PER
B.	I-PER
English	I-PER

Rainsville	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Alabama	I-LOC

**Towns	O
:	O
'	O
''	O
Hypoluxo	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
,	O
'	O
''	O
Juno	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
''	O
'	O
,	O
and	O
'	O
''	O
Jupiter	B-LOC
''	O
'	O

in	O
the	O
early	O
1990s	O
and	O
then	O
The	B-ORG
Computer	I-ORG
Paper	I-ORG
from	O
the	O
mid-1990s	O
up	O
until	O
2003	O
.	O

A	O
Blockhaus	B-ORG
was	O
constructed	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
extensive	O
entrenchments	O
.	O

'	O
''	O
Pat	B-PER
Cash	I-PER
''	O
'	O
defeated	O
Brad	B-PER
Gilbert	I-PER
7–6	O
,	O
4–6	O
,	O
2–6	O
,	O
6–0	O
,	O
6–1	O

On	O
29	O
November	O
2009	O
,	O
he	O
netted	O
the	O
first	O
goal	O
in	O
a	O
4–2	O
victory	O
over	O
Grêmio	B-ORG
Recreativo	I-ORG
Barueri	I-ORG
.	O

John	B-PER
H.	I-PER
McClendon	I-PER
,	O
African-American	B-ORG
studies	O
scholar	O
at	O
Michigan	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
University	I-ORG

UC	B-ORG
Irvine	I-ORG
Medical	I-ORG
Center	I-ORG
,	O
in	O
Orange	B-LOC
;	O

Givanildo	B-PER
Oliveira	I-PER
(	O
Aug	O
1	O
,	O
2006	O
–	O
Dec	O
6	O
,	O
2006	O
)	O

**	O
''	O
''	O
by	O
Antonio	B-PER
Pietrangeli	I-PER

He	O
represented	O
Sri	B-ORG
Lanka	I-ORG
A	I-ORG
.	O

Pittsburgh	B-ORG
Penguins	I-ORG
–	O
87	O
points	O

He	O
has	O
played	O
for	O
Real	B-ORG
Estelí	I-ORG
since	O
2010	O
.	O

As	O
U.S.	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Exchange	I-ORG
Commission	I-ORG
(	O
SEC	O
)	O
Info	O
notes	O
:	O

*2005	O
/	O
06	O
Anwil	B-ORG
Włocławek	I-ORG
(	O
PLK	B-ORG
)	O
-	O
Coach	O
assistant	O

04	O
)	O
,	O
Mike	B-PER
Garvey	I-PER
(	O
No	O
.	O

Shepperton	B-ORG
Branch	I-ORG
Line	I-ORG

Gail	B-PER
Mancuso	I-PER
(	O
2	O
episodes	O
)	O

He	O
was	O
previously	O
married	O
to	O
DeShawn	B-ORG
Snow	I-ORG
.	O

The	O
property	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
Hammermill	B-ORG
Paper	I-ORG
,	O
which	O
began	O
operations	O
under	O
the	O
Allegheny	B-ORG
Railroad	I-ORG
name	O
on	O
September	O
3	O
,	O
1985	O
.	O

He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Alcoa	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Tennessee	I-LOC
.	O

'	O
''	O
Andy	B-PER
Murray	I-PER
[6]	O

Apologize]]	O
''	O
by	O
OneRepublic	B-ORG
feat	O
.	O

*Mixed	O
at	O
Ardent	B-ORG
Studios	I-ORG
,	O
Memphis	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Tennessee	I-LOC
in	O
June	O
1999	O

'	O
''	O
Romolo	B-PER
Ferri	I-PER
''	O
'	O

Wish	B-ORG
I	I-ORG
May	I-ORG

Igor	B-PER
Kurchatov	I-PER
,	O
the	O
leader	O
of	O
the	O
Soviet	B-ORG
atomic	I-ORG
bomb	I-ORG
project	I-ORG
.	O

She	O
guest	O
starred	O
in	O
5	O
episodes	O
of	O
Supah	B-ORG
Ninjas	I-ORG
''	O
and	O
also	O
appeared	O
in	O
The	B-ORG
Aquabats	I-ORG
!	I-ORG
Super	I-ORG
Show	I-ORG
!	I-ORG
''	O
.	O

``	O
All	B-ORG
I	I-ORG
Have	I-ORG
to	I-ORG
Do	I-ORG
is	I-ORG
Dream	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
with	O
Laurent	B-PER
Voulzy	I-PER
)	O

Randolph	B-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
for	O
grades	O
9-12	O
(	O
1,641	O
students	O
)	O

This	O
marriage	O
would	O
produce	O
the	O
progeny	O
of	O
Kartam	B-PER
of	I-PER
Colchis	I-PER
.	O

''le	O
Cirque	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
Gavarnie	I-LOC
''	O

Thomas	B-PER
Koch	I-PER
(	I-PER
ice	I-PER
hockey	I-PER
)	I-PER

Seve	B-PER
Ballesteros	I-PER
:	O
1981	O
,	O
1985	O
,	O
1995	O

*The	O
Essence	O
of	O
the	O
Shari'ah	B-ORG

BZL1-3452	O
Freedom	B-ORG
at	I-ORG
Point	I-ORG
Zero	I-ORG
''	O
by	O
Jefferson	B-ORG
Starship	I-ORG

It	O
was	O
released	O
in	O
September	O
1993	O
as	O
the	O
fourth	O
single	O
from	O
the	O
album	O
Mark	B-ORG
Collie	I-ORG
''	O
.	O

''	O
Star	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
''	O

Infusion	B-ORG
–	O
producer	O
,	O
remixing	O

She	O
played	O
for	O
the	O
:	O
Racine	B-ORG
Belles	I-ORG
(	O
in	O
1949	O
)	O
Grand	B-ORG
Rapids	I-ORG
Chicks	I-ORG
(	O
in	O
1950	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rockford	B-ORG
Peaches	I-ORG
(	O
in	O
1950	O
)	O
.	O

On	O
November	O
12	O
,	O
2015	O
,	O
Margaret	B-PER
Qualley	I-PER
began	O
negotiations	O
for	O
the	O
female	O
lead	O
.	O

Westbury	B-ORG
Christian	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
(	O
Houston	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
TX	I-ORG
)	O
(	O
2005	O
,	O
2009	O
)	O

High	B-LOC
Performance	I-LOC
Computing	I-LOC
Center	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Stuttgart	I-LOC
,	O
2015	O

Pipes	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Drums	I-ORG
of	O
the	O
Royal	B-ORG
Scots	I-ORG
Dragoon	I-ORG
Guards	I-ORG

St	B-ORG
Patrick	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
Athletic	I-ORG
won	O
the	O
League	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Ireland	I-ORG

Union	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	O
Arkansas	B-LOC
(	O
northeast	O
)	O

Three	O
years	O
later	O
the	O
family	O
moved	O
to	O
Prineville	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Oregon	I-LOC
.	O

Ekaterina	B-PER
Bobrova	I-PER
/	O
Dmitri	B-PER
Soloviev	I-PER
Ekaterina	B-PER
Riazanova	I-PER
/	O
Ilia	B-PER
Tkachenko	I-PER
Ekaterina	B-PER
Pushkash	I-PER
/	O
Jonathan	B-PER
Guerreiro	I-PER

''	O
Belize	B-ORG
Premier	I-ORG
League	I-ORG
:	O
3	O
'	O
''	O

====Ichthyodectid	O
(	O
Ichthyodectidae	B-LOC
)	O
====	O

Rain	B-PER
-	O
``	O
Ways	B-ORG
To	I-ORG
Avoid	I-ORG
The	I-ORG
Sun	I-ORG
''	O

*Election	O
of	O
the	O
Central	B-ORG
Executive	I-ORG
Committee	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Ukraine	I-ORG

William	B-PER
T.	I-PER
``	I-PER
Bloody	I-PER
Bill	I-PER
''	I-PER
Anderson	I-PER

Tristan	B-PER
Venus	I-PER
Antico	I-PER
.	O

Uriel	B-ORG
Acosta	I-ORG
,	O
(	O
1585–1640	O
)	O

He	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
original	O
founders	O
of	O
the	O
Alliance	B-ORG
israélite	I-ORG
universelle	I-ORG
(	O
AIU	O
)	O
.	O

Ohio	B-ORG
Valley	I-ORG
Filk	I-ORG
Fest	I-ORG

Cordillera	B-LOC
Province	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Chile	I-LOC

Archived	O
from	O
the	O
original	O
by	O
the	O
Internet	B-ORG
Archive	I-ORG
,	O
20	O
April	O
2007	O
.	O

Ram	B-PER
Charan	I-PER
Teja	I-PER
,	O
Neha	B-PER
Sharma	I-PER

:	O
''Portrayed	O
by	O
:	O
''	O
Desiree	B-ORG
Del	I-ORG
Valle	I-ORG

Elahi	B-PER
Bux	I-PER
Soomro	I-PER

'	O
''	O
Rick	B-PER
Leach	I-PER
''	O
'	O
/	O
'	O
''	O
Jim	B-PER
Pugh	I-PER
''	O
'	O
defeated	O
Paul	B-PER
Chamberlin	I-PER
/	O
Paul	B-PER
Wekesa	I-PER
6–3	O
,	O
6–4	O

*2011	O
Vienna	B-ORG
Fashion	I-ORG
Award	I-ORG
for	O
''Best	O
Designer	O
Branding	O
''	O

''	O
'With	O
Sassy	B-PER
Stephie	I-PER
''	O
'	O

Fife	B-PER
Symington	I-PER
III	I-PER
(	O
1991–1997	O
)	O

:	O
:	O
''	O
'Winners	O
:	O
'	O
''	O
Distillery	B-ORG
1	O
-	O
0	O
Cliftonville	B-ORG

He	O
was	O
born	O
near	O
Poitiers	B-LOC
in	O
1752	O
.	O

Amara	B-LOC
fusca	I-LOC
''	O
Dejean	O
,	O
1828	O

Vaqueras	B-ORG
de	I-ORG
Bayamón	I-ORG
(	O
2007	O
)	O

There	O
are	O
concessions	O
in	O
some	O
branches	O
of	O
Selfridges	B-ORG
and	O
Fenwick	B-ORG
.	O

Georges	B-PER
Bataille	I-PER
(	O
1897-1962	O
)	O
.	O

Eventually	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
subsequently	O
killed	O
by	O
Marlo	B-PER
Stanfield	I-PER
's	O
crew	O
.	O

Connel	B-ORG
Bridge	I-ORG
completed	O
in	O
1903	O

Hundreds	O
of	O
people	O
demonstrated	O
on	O
Chicago	B-LOC
's	O
Michigan	B-ORG
Avenue	I-ORG
on	O
March	O
19	O
.	O

'	O
''	O
Equivocations	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
:	O
making	O
an	O
indirect	O
,	O
ambiguous	O
,	O
or	O
contradictory	O
statement	O
.	O

Torrent	B-LOC
tyrannulet	I-LOC
,	O
'	O
''	O
'	O

Helmut	B-PER
Schmidt	I-PER
(	O
1982	O
)	O

Palace	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Auburn	I-ORG
Hills	I-ORG
7,230	O

Mitch	B-PER
Kupchak	I-PER
,	O
Washington	B-ORG
Bullets	I-ORG

J.	B-ORG
C.	I-ORG
Williamson	I-ORG
Ltd	I-ORG
.	I-ORG

The	B-ORG
Kingsmen	I-ORG
released	O
a	O
version	O
on	O
their	O
1966	O
album	O
Up	B-ORG
And	I-ORG
Away	I-ORG
''	O
.	O

''	O
Uí	B-PER
Maine	I-PER
''	O
'	O
–	O
Murchadh	B-PER
mac	I-PER
Sochlachan	I-PER
(	O
909–936	O
)	O

Lori	B-PER
McNeil	I-PER
/	O
Mercedes	B-PER
Paz	I-PER
''	O
(	O
Quarterfinals	O
)	O

*Track	O
6	O
recorded	O
direct	O
to	O
DAT	B-ORG
from	O
MIDI-instruments	B-ORG
by	O
Tim	B-PER
Hodgkinson	I-PER

Jim	B-PER
O'Toole	I-PER
(	O
1	O
)	O

Spain	B-LOC
(	O
Televisión	B-ORG
Española	I-ORG
)	O

Coach	O
106	O
was	O
constructed	O
in	O
1913	O
by	O
the	O
Canadian	B-ORG
Pacific	I-ORG
Railway	I-ORG
at	O
Angus	B-ORG
Shops	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Quebec	I-ORG
.	O

'	O
''	O
Vielist	B-LOC
''	O
'	O

''Kunst	O
''	O
was	O
released	O
on	O
February	O
26	O
,	O
2013	O
on	O
Metropolis	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG
.	O

Inactivated	O
1	O
November	O
1921	O
at	O
Danville	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
West	I-LOC
Virginia	I-LOC
.	O

Japan	B-ORG
Business	I-ORG
Federation	I-ORG

Better	B-LOC
Loosen	I-LOC
Up	I-LOC
(	O
2004	O
)	O

The	O
final	O
was	O
contested	O
by	O
Stephen	B-PER
Hendry	I-PER
and	O
Jimmy	B-PER
White	I-PER
.	O

As	O
noted	O
by	O
Mark	B-PER
Evanier	I-PER
:	O

George	B-PER
Peter	I-PER
Alexander	I-PER
Healy	I-PER

It	O
introduce	O
Cable	B-ORG
TV	I-ORG
in	O
2000	O
.	O

Janine	B-PER
Butcher	I-PER
(	O
Charlie	B-PER
Brooks	I-PER
)	O

It	O
is	O
managed	O
by	O
Birmingham	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
Council	I-ORG
.	O

James	B-PER
J.	I-PER
Belden	I-PER

President	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Swiss	I-ORG
Confederation	I-ORG
,	O
1990	O
and	O
1997	O

He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Veghel	B-LOC
,	O
The	B-ORG
Netherlands	I-ORG
,	O
on	O
18	O
December	O
1960	O
.	O

Queen	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Business	I-ORG
,	O
Queen	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
University	I-ORG

He	O
was	O
the	O
United	B-ORG
States	I-ORG
ambassador	I-ORG
to	O
Mauritania	B-LOC
from	O
1971	O
to	O
1974	O
,	O
to	O
Syria	B-LOC
from	O
1974	O
to	O
78	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Philippines	B-LOC
from	O
1978	O
to	O
1981	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Saudi	B-LOC
Arabia	I-LOC
from	O
1981	O
to	O
1983	O
.	O

He	O
turned	O
down	O
the	O
offer	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
I	B-ORG
'm	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Celebrity	I-ORG
...	I-ORG
Get	I-ORG
Me	I-ORG
out	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Here	I-ORG
!	I-ORG
in	O
2004	O
.	O

Paulo	B-PER
Thiago	I-PER
-	O
(	O
UFC	B-ORG
,	O
Jungle	B-ORG
Fight	I-ORG
)	O

University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Arts	I-ORG
London	I-ORG

Girl	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
Pharrell	I-ORG
Williams	I-ORG
album	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Danny	B-PER
Granger	I-PER
(	O
28	O
)	O

Also	O
partly	O
covered	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	B-LOC
Borough	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Greenwich	I-LOC

''	O
Melo	B-LOC
melo	I-LOC
''	O

Kočín	B-LOC
(	I-LOC
Plzeň-North	I-LOC
District	I-LOC
)	I-LOC

Events	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
'	O
''	O
1771	O
in	O
Norway	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
.	O

Firstly	O
in	O
Tajikistan	B-LOC
in	O
July	O
3,500	O
were	O
killed	O
.	O

Phyllocoma	B-LOC
scalariformis	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Broderip	O
,	O
1833	O
)	O

Frankie	B-ORG
Lymon	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Teenagers	I-ORG

Since	O
1996	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Danube-Auen	B-ORG
National	I-ORG
Park	I-ORG
.	O

Embassy	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Canada	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Washington	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
D.C	I-ORG
.	I-ORG

A.H.	B-PER
Reed	I-PER
–	O
publisher	O

It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Seychelles	B-LOC
.	O

Wander	B-PER
Johannes	I-PER
de	I-PER
Haas	I-PER

35th	B-ORG
Tactical	I-ORG
Fighter	I-ORG
Squadron	I-ORG
1963–1967	O

Günter	B-PER
Schulz	I-PER
(	O
1	O
,	O
3	O
)	O

WEC	B-ORG
Featherweight	I-ORG
Champion	I-ORG
(	O
One	O
time	O
;	O
Final	O
)	O

Barbara	B-PER
Grizzuti	I-PER
Harrison	I-PER
for	O
''Italian	O
Days	O
''	O

20	O
James	B-PER
White	I-PER
–	O
''Junior	O
''	O

**C	O
Amar'e	B-PER
Stoudemire	I-PER
-	O
Phoenix	B-ORG
Suns	I-ORG

He	O
supported	O
the	O
Socialist	B-ORG
Party	I-ORG
for	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
years	O
,	O
before	O
joining	O
The	B-ORG
Greens	I-ORG
.	O

In	O
1885	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
elected	O
to	O
the	O
Maryland	B-ORG
House	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Delegates	I-ORG
,	O
and	O
twice	O
re-elected	O
.	O

Osterley	B-ORG
Park	I-ORG
is	O
a	O
mile	O
to	O
the	O
north-east	O
.	O

|	O
Wilde	B-PER
Oscar	I-PER
''West	O
Side	O
''	O

She	O
was	O
sold	O
in	O
1946	O
and	O
renamed	O
''Speedon	O
''	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
broken	O
up	O
at	O
Aden	B-LOC
in	O
1957	O
.	O

(	O
Broadcast	O
on	O
ABC	B-ORG
Radio	I-ORG
National	I-ORG
,	O
1980	O
)	O

181–	O
Junri	B-PER
Namigata	I-PER
–	O
2008	O

30	O
US	B-ORG
dollars	I-ORG
,	O
payable	O
on	O
arrival	O
.	O

1	O
chair	O
turned	O
Default	O
to	O
Sarah	B-PER
Geronimo	I-PER

This	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
combined	O
with	O
a	O
possible	O
role	O
in	O
Joseph	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Amazing	I-ORG
Technicolor	I-ORG
Dreamcoat	I-ORG
,	O
but	O
making	O
a	O
voluntary	O
exit	O
was	O
necessary	O
.	O

''	O
Utricularia	B-LOC
rostrata	I-LOC
''	O
A.Fleischm	O
.	O

She	O
won	O
the	O
Baringo	B-ORG
15	I-ORG
km	I-ORG
Road	I-ORG
Race	I-ORG
in	O
2007	O
,	O
finishing	O
in	O
a	O
time	O
of	O
50:52	O
.	O

''To	O
Sail	O
,	O
To	O
Sail	O
''	O
on	O
Tzadik	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG
.	O

Jiangsu	B-ORG
Normal	I-ORG
University	I-ORG

Citrus	B-LOC
Heights	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
California	I-LOC

Elida	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Ohio	I-LOC

Trauma	B-ORG
:	I-ORG
Life	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
E.R	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
''	O

He	O
was	O
raised	O
in	O
South	B-LOC
Florida	I-LOC
,	O
where	O
he	O
attended	O
the	O
Chaminade-Madonna	B-ORG
College	I-ORG
Preparatory	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
in	O
Hollywood	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Florida	I-LOC
.	O

1131	O
Oneida	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Pennsylvania	I-LOC
$	O
18,756	O

The	O
cuts	O
prompted	O
at	O
least	O
one	O
angry	O
outburst	O
in	O
Dáil	B-ORG
Éireann	I-ORG
.	O

Khull	B-LOC
(	I-LOC
Noor-abad	I-LOC
)	I-LOC

Bryan	B-PER
Adams	I-PER
–	O
``	O
There	B-ORG
Will	I-ORG
Never	I-ORG
Be	I-ORG
Another	I-ORG
Tonight	I-ORG
''	O

Puskás	B-ORG
Ferenc	I-ORG
Stadium	I-ORG
,	O
Budapest	B-LOC
,	O
Hungary	B-LOC

He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Gehren	B-LOC
.	O

Voters	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
polls	O
to	O
elect	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
federal	B-ORG
level	O
:	O

Max	B-ORG
Karl	I-ORG
Ernst	I-ORG
Ludwig	I-ORG
Planck	I-ORG
(	O
1858–1947	O
)	O

Nihad	B-PER
Hasanović	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1974	O
)	O
,	O
writer	O
and	O
translator	O

Synchronised	B-ORG
Swimmers	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2009	O
)	O

In	O
September	O
2007	O
the	O
band	O
released	O
Please	B-ORG
Experience	I-ORG
Wolfmother	I-ORG
Live	I-ORG
''	O
,	O
their	O
first	O
live	B-ORG
video	I-ORG
album	I-ORG
.	O

Their	O
conclusion	O
,	O
published	O
in	O
the	O
American	B-ORG
Journal	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Education	I-ORG
''	O
,	O
was	O
that	O
:	O

The	O
last	O
regular	O
religious	O
use	O
was	O
by	O
Free	B-ORG
Methodists	I-ORG
in	O
the	O
early	O
1920s	O
.	O

Juha	B-PER
Malinen	I-PER
(	O
June	O
5	O
,	O
2013	O
–	O
Dec	O
31	O
,	O
2013	O
)	O

**	O
Universal	B-ORG
Studios	I-ORG
begins	O
operating	O
.	O

He	O
died	O
in	O
1940	O
at	O
Beaconsfield	B-LOC
.	O

Öser	B-ORG
(	O
born	O
1966	O
)	O

Jason	B-PER
Bateman	I-PER
,	O
Amber	B-PER
Tamblyn	I-PER
,	O
and	O
Smokey	B-PER
Robinson	I-PER

La	B-LOC
Grange	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Missouri	I-LOC

1978	O
Garryowen	B-ORG
-	O
Midleton	B-ORG
17-15	O

Tom	B-PER
Kite	I-PER
,	O
Greg	B-PER
Norman	I-PER

San	B-LOC
Juan	I-LOC
de	I-LOC
la	I-LOC
Nava	I-LOC

'	O
''	O
Philipp	B-PER
Oswald	I-PER
''	O
'	O
'	O
''	O
Mate	B-PER
Pavić	I-PER
''	O
'	O

Rice	B-ORG
House	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Bentonville	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Arkansas	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
,	O
listed	B-ORG
on	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
NRHP	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
Benton	I-ORG
County	I-ORG

forfeit	O
1716–1853	O
,	O
also	O
Earl	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Melfort	I-ORG
1853–1902	O

Ameri	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Tangestan	I-LOC

Gertrude	B-PER
Stein	I-PER
,	O
author	O
.	O

October	B-ORG
2012	I-ORG
Jordanian–Syrian	I-ORG
border	I-ORG
clash	I-ORG

Jamie	B-PER
Baulch	I-PER
,	O
Daniel	B-PER
Caines	I-PER
,	O
Jared	B-PER
Deacon	I-PER
,	O
and	O
Iwan	B-PER
Thomas	I-PER

``	B-ORG
Tongue	I-ORG
Tied	I-ORG
''	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Grouplove	I-ORG
song	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
,	O
2011	O

Anthony	B-PER
Armstrong	I-PER
,	O
NFL	B-ORG
player	O

Irv	B-PER
Noren	I-PER
,	O
OF	O
,	O
1959	O
,	O
1960	O

He	O
founded	O
what	O
became	O
the	O
Moscow	B-LOC
Philharmonic	I-LOC
Orchestra	I-LOC
in	O
1951	O
.	O

Lucie	B-PER
Höflich	I-PER
as	O
Herzogin-Mutter	O

Whole	B-ORG
Earth	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

''	O
'Top	O
Scorer	O
(	O
s	O
)	O
:	O
'	O
''	O
John	B-PER
Kosmina	I-PER
(	O
Sydney	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
–	O
23	O
goals	O
)	O

Computer	B-ORG
Science	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Engineering	I-ORG
(	O
60	O
Seats	O
)	O
.	O

Thomas	B-ORG
Fust	I-ORG
(	O
or	O
Fusse	O
)	O

Professor	O
at	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Illinois	I-ORG

T.	B-PER
E.	I-PER
Lawrence	I-PER
rediscovered	O
the	O
book	O
and	O
caused	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
republished	O
in	O
the	O
1920s	O
,	O
contributing	O
an	O
admiring	O
introduction	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O

``	O
Grown	B-ORG
Up	I-ORG
Christmas	I-ORG
List	I-ORG
''	O

He	O
died	O
in	O
Florida	B-LOC
in	O
1973	O
.	O

Warlock	B-ORG
-	O
Triumph	B-ORG
And	I-ORG
Agony	I-ORG
''	O

Work	O
colleagues	O
and	O
friends	O
from	O
Northamptonshire	B-LOC

The	O
mini-tournament	O
will	O
be	O
hosted	O
in	O
Montenegro	B-LOC
.	O

Apple	B-ORG
Corps	I-ORG
v.	I-ORG
Apple	B-ORG
Computer	I-ORG
''	O

In	O
1996	O
,	O
she	O
released	O
her	O
first	O
album	O
,	O
Takin	B-ORG
'	I-ORG
Mine	I-ORG
''	O
.	O

Mancos	B-LOC
Group	I-LOC
/	O
Gullup	B-LOC
Formation	I-LOC

'	O
''	O
Camille	B-PER
Serme	I-PER
''	O
'11-7	O
,	O
17-15	O
,	O
9-11	O
,	O
11-8	O

Pet	B-ORG
Shop	I-ORG
Boys	I-ORG
-	O
``	O
I	B-ORG
'm	I-ORG
With	I-ORG
Stupid	I-ORG
''	O

Panzer	B-ORG
Division	I-ORG
Marduk	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1999	O
)	O

*2005	O
:	O
''Simple	O
-	O
Si	B-ORG
demain	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
turn	I-ORG
around	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
''	O

Steven	B-PER
S.	I-PER
Levitan	I-PER

She	O
sang	O
the	O
role	O
for	O
her	O
first	O
appearance	O
at	O
the	O
Hamburg	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Opera	I-ORG
in	O
1963	O
and	O
at	O
both	O
the	O
Deutsche	B-ORG
Oper	I-ORG
Berlin	I-ORG
and	O
the	O
Vienna	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Opera	I-ORG
in	O
1964	O
.	O

Baltimore	B-PER
County	I-PER
State	I-PER
's	I-PER
Attorney	I-PER

:	O
Personnel	O
and	O
equipment	O
assigned	O
to	O
:	O
75th	B-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Transport	I-ORG
Squadron	I-ORG
(	O
Reactivated	O
)	O
,	O
20	O
July	O
1952	O
–	O
16	O
May	O
1953	O

Aliyu	B-PER
Modibbo	I-PER
Umar	I-PER
(	O
July	O
2007	O
-	O
Oct	O
2008	O
)	O
Adamu	B-PER
Aliero	I-PER
(	O
Dec	O
2008	O
-	O
March	O
2010	O
)	O

Donglin	B-ORG
Temple	I-ORG
,	O
Jiangxi	B-LOC
,	O
China	B-LOC

Naiqama	B-PER
,	I-PER
Wes	I-PER
.	O

Bataan	B-ORG
Export	I-ORG
Processing	I-ORG
Zone	I-ORG

Włodzisław	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Goleniów	I-LOC
County	I-LOC

This	O
album	O
consists	O
of	O
three	O
parts	O
:	O
Twenity	B-ORG
1991-1996	I-ORG
''	O
,	O
Twenity	B-ORG
1997-1999	I-ORG
''	O
,	O
and	O
Twenity	B-ORG
2000-2010	I-ORG
''	O
.	O

Please	B-ORG
Give	I-ORG
Me	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Job	I-ORG
!	I-ORG
''	O

Bethanie	B-PER
Mattek-Sands	I-PER
7–6	O
(	O
6	O
)	O
,	O
2–6	O
,	O
7–5	O

He	O
was	O
a	O
councillor	O
on	O
Watford	B-ORG
Borough	I-ORG
Council	I-ORG
from	O
1990	O
to	O
1994	O
.	O

``	O
What	B-ORG
Can	I-ORG
I	I-ORG
Do	I-ORG
?	I-ORG
''	O

50	O
Chevrolet	B-ORG
in	O
place	O
of	O
Randy	B-PER
LaJoie	I-PER
,	O
who	O
had	O
Busch	B-ORG
Grand	I-ORG
National	I-ORG
obligations	O
at	O
Pikes	B-ORG
Peak	I-ORG
International	I-ORG
Raceway	I-ORG
in	O
his	O
No	O
.	O

Gimnasia	B-ORG
y	I-ORG
Esgrima	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
LP	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
(	O
2014	O
)	O

'	O
''	O
Grigori	B-PER
Gorin	I-PER
''	O
'	O
(	O
1940-2000	O
)	O

San	B-LOC
Diego	I-LOC
–	O
''29.7	O
%	O
''	O

Páll	B-PER
Ólafsson	I-PER
(	I-PER
handballer	I-PER
)	I-PER

The	O
vessel	O
's	O
sister	O
ship	O
was	O
''Orcades	B-ORG
''	I-ORG
,	O
launched	O
in	O
1937	O
.	O

Bosnia-Herzegovina	B-ORG
1–0	O
(	O
0–0	O
)	O
Belgium	B-ORG

Luc	B-PER
Siméon	I-PER
Auguste	I-PER
Dagobert	I-PER

St.	B-ORG
Joseph	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
In	I-ORG
Tanzania	I-ORG

'	O
''	O
Judging	B-ORG
Amy	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
(	O
23	O
/	O
14.09	O
million	O
)	O

Zoe	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
Duncan	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Jack	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Jane	I-ORG
''	O

Norton	B-ORG
Rose	I-ORG
Fulbright	I-ORG

Defeated	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Tennessee	I-LOC

Berkeley	B-ORG
Mall	I-ORG
–	O
Goldsboro	B-LOC

Notes	O
:	O
generally	O
supposed	O
to	O
represent	O
William	B-PER
Ewart	I-PER
Gladstone	I-PER

Matt	B-PER
Hoopes	I-PER
wrote	O
the	O
song	O
.	O

He	O
formerly	O
played	O
for	O
Glasgow	B-ORG
Warriors	I-ORG
.	O

;	O
'	O
''	O
3rd	B-ORG
Brigade	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
:	O

1606-1638	O
:	O
Antoine	B-PER
de	I-PER
Loménie	I-PER

Cícero]]	O
(	O
Figueirense	B-ORG
FC	I-ORG
)	O

Lito	B-PER
Lapid	I-PER
,	O
Bernard	B-PER
Bonnin	I-PER

He	O
was	O
also	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
European	B-ORG
Coal	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Steel	I-ORG
Committee	I-ORG
from	O
1992	O
to	O
2002	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
International	B-ORG
Metalworkers	I-ORG
'	I-ORG
Federation	I-ORG
.	O

95	O
,	O
by	O
Alun	B-PER
Hoddinott	I-PER
(	O
1977	O
)	O

Janaki	B-ORG
Yugantar	I-ORG
English	I-ORG
Boarding	I-ORG
School	I-ORG

''	O
Cannon	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
TV	I-ORG
series	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1971–1975	O
)	O

Vampire	B-PER
Warrior	I-PER
(	O
1995	O
)	O

It	O
resurfaced	O
in	O
its	O
entirety	O
on	O
the	O
October	O
2000	O
album	O
,	O
Who	B-ORG
Is	I-ORG
Dr	I-ORG
Who	B-ORG
''	O
.	O

Sylvester	B-PER
,	I-PER
James	I-PER
Joseph	I-PER

On	O
7	O
July	O
1828	O
he	O
was	O
performing	O
at	O
Vauxhall	B-ORG
Gardens	I-ORG
.	O

John	B-PER
Fegan	I-PER
(	I-PER
rugby	I-PER
union	I-PER
)	I-PER

LNM	B-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Information	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG

Bernard	B-PER
F.	I-PER
Martin	I-PER
,	O
(	O
1845-1914	O
)	O

Journal	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
International	I-ORG
Financial	I-ORG
Management	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Accounting	I-ORG
''	O

*Animation	O
:	O
Tom	B-PER
Ray	I-PER
,	O
Dick	B-PER
Thompson	I-PER
,	O
Ben	B-PER
Washam	I-PER
,	O
Ken	B-PER
Harris	I-PER
,	O
Don	B-PER
Towsley	I-PER
,	O
Phil	B-PER
Roman	I-PER

He	O
teaches	O
at	O
Salem	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
College	I-ORG
.	O

''	O
Children	B-ORG
in	I-ORG
Need	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1980–present	O
)	O

Vice	B-ORG
Premier	I-ORG
-	O
Liu	B-PER
Chao-shiuan	I-PER

He	O
died	O
on	O
December	O
24	O
,	O
2010	O
in	O
Tempe	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Arizona	I-LOC
.	O

It	O
was	O
written	O
by	O
Graham	B-PER
Roland	I-PER
and	O
directed	O
by	O
Eagle	B-PER
Egilsson	I-PER
.	O

The	B-ORG
Times	I-ORG
proclaimed	O
it	O
as	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
Copernican	B-ORG
Principle	I-ORG
.	O

Astrakhan	B-LOC
Oblast	I-LOC
:	O
Alexander	B-PER
Zhilkin	I-PER
(	O
since	O
2004	O
)	O
,	O
Anatoly	B-PER
Guzhvin	I-PER
(	O
1991–2004	O
)	O

In	O
the	O
Museum	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
City	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
New	I-ORG
York	I-ORG

Evgeny	B-PER
Korolev	I-PER
Marcel	B-ORG
Granollers-Pujol	I-ORG
Filippo	B-PER
Volandri	I-PER
Alberto	B-PER
Martín	I-PER

x-	O
''	O
Sudbury	B-ORG
Wolves	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

OMEGA	B-LOC
Navigation	I-LOC
System	I-LOC
,	O
1971–1997	O

**	O
''	O
Le	B-ORG
Roi	I-ORG
de	I-ORG
Lahore	I-ORG
''	O

''Gospel	O
''	O
,	O
an	O
album	O
by	O
The	B-ORG
Marshall	I-ORG
Tucker	I-ORG
Band	I-ORG

890	B-ORG
Naval	I-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Squadron	I-ORG
.	O

National	B-ORG
Theatre	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
Belgrade	I-ORG
,	O
founded	O
in	O
1868	O
.	O

It	O
was	O
released	O
in	O
2006	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
by	O
Rotana	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG
.	O

Solomon	B-PER
Van	I-PER
Rensselaer	I-PER
(	O
F	O
)	O
,	O
until	O
January	O
14	O
,	O
1822	O

He	O
transferred	O
to	O
Brunswick	B-ORG
Juventus	I-ORG
later	O
on	O
.	O

List	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
mammals	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
Saint	I-ORG
Pierre	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Miquelon	I-ORG

*Photograph	O
of	O
:	O
Paris	B-LOC
,	O
France	B-LOC
and	O
Lyon	B-LOC
,	O
France	B-LOC

Koo	B-LOC
Wee	I-LOC
Rup	I-LOC
North	I-LOC
3891	O

Stresemann	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
bushcrow	I-LOC

Katharine	B-PER
Susannah	I-PER
Prichard	I-PER
—	O
''Windlestraws	O
''	O

Bogor	B-ORG
Agricultural	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
,	O
Bogor	B-LOC

''Metalasia	O
''	O
is	O
also	O
found	O
in	O
KwaZulu-Natal	B-LOC
,	O
Free	B-LOC
State	I-LOC
,	O
Eastern	B-LOC
Cape	I-LOC
and	O
Lesotho	B-LOC
.	O

Showcases	O
have	O
occurred	O
in	O
Brazil	B-LOC
and	O
Colombia	B-LOC
as	O
well	O
.	O

Orlando	B-PER
Bloom	I-PER
,	O
Riley	B-PER
Keough	I-PER
,	O
Taraji	B-PER
P.	I-PER
Henson	I-PER
,	O
Rob	B-PER
Morrow	I-PER
,	O
Michael	B-PER
Peña	I-PER

It	O
lies	O
on	O
the	O
A1079	B-ORG
road	I-ORG
.	O

On	O
21	O
June	O
2006	O
,	O
he	O
managed	O
to	O
score	O
a	O
goal	O
against	O
Ivory	B-ORG
Coast	I-ORG
in	O
a	O
thrilling	O
3–2	O
match	O
,	O
eventually	O
won	O
by	O
the	O
opposition	O
at	O
Allianz	B-ORG
Arena	I-ORG
.	O

``	O
Towering	B-ORG
Toccata	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
Johann	B-PER
Sebastian	I-PER
Bach	I-PER
)	O
-	O
5:04	O

Maple	B-ORG
Grove	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Dufferin	I-ORG
County	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Ontario	I-ORG

Lyric	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
US	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

alt=Green	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
purple	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
yellow	I-LOC
and	I-LOC
orange	I-LOC
map	I-LOC

Athene	B-PER
Seyler	I-PER
as	O
Mrs.	O
Durland	O

University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Toronto	I-ORG
Faculty	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Applied	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Engineering	I-ORG

Chandrasekhar	B-PER
as	O
Rathnavel	O
,	O
Poonjolai	O
's	O
father	O

In	O
1926	O
he	O
accepted	O
an	O
assistant	O
professorship	O
,	O
a	O
position	O
previously	O
held	O
by	O
Albert	B-PER
Schweitzer	I-PER
.	O

``	O
Maybellene	B-ORG
''	O
–	O
Chuck	B-PER
Berry	I-PER
(	O
1955	O
)	O

*Offensive	O
Newcomer	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
:	O
Charles	B-PER
Sims	I-PER
,	O
West	B-LOC
Virginia	I-LOC

;	O
Became	O
Prince	B-PER
Kachō	I-PER
Hirotada	I-PER

Later	O
he	O
was	O
buried	O
alongside	O
Luis	B-PER
Otero	I-PER
Cifuentes	I-PER
and	O
Alfonso	B-PER
Jacquin	I-PER
.	O

edited	O
and	O
with	O
an	O
introduction	O
by	O
Anthony	B-PER
Burgess	I-PER
.	O

Peter	B-PER
Buchanan	I-PER
(	I-PER
architect	I-PER
)	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1942	O
)	O

She	O
is	O
also	O
Princess	B-PER
of	I-PER
Wales	I-PER
but	O
does	O
not	O
use	O
that	O
title	O
.	O

Star	B-ORG
Trek	I-ORG
:	I-ORG
Deep	I-ORG
Space	I-ORG
Nine	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1997	O
)	O

Leena	B-PER
Peltonen-Palotie	I-PER
(	O
1952	O
–	O
2010	O
)	O

Peter	B-PER
M.	I-PER
Shane	I-PER
,	O
1994–1998	O

UKS4	O
:	O
Limavady	B-ORG
District	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
United	I-ORG
Kingdom	I-ORG

**	O
In	B-PER
Living	I-PER
Color	I-PER
,	O
''	O
(	O
Fox	B-ORG
)	O

Katy	B-PER
Clark	I-PER
(	O
lost	O
seat	O
2015	O
)	O

''Body	B-LOC
and	I-LOC
Soul	I-LOC
''	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
Coleman	I-LOC
Hawkins	I-LOC
album	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
,	O
1994	O

Musashi	B-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
(	O
Tokyo	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
)	O

'	O
''	O
Redcar	B-LOC
''	O
'	O

``	O
Cry	B-ORG
For	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Shadow	I-ORG
''	O

*Ferrian	O
,	O
member	O
of	O
Wildcore	B-ORG
.	O

Garry	B-PER
Galley	I-PER
:	O
2014–present	O

Kathy	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER
Anne	B-PER
Smith	I-PER
4–6	O
,	O
7–5	O
,	O
6–1	O

The	O
Six	O
were	O
featured	O
on	O
the	O
Gorgon	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
track	O
``	O
Take	B-ORG
It	I-ORG
All	I-ORG
.	O

Tom	B-PER
Weiskopf	I-PER
(	O
7	O
)	O

*8	O
Oct	O
-	O
William	B-PER
M.	I-PER
Boyle	I-PER

''	O
VINA	B-PER
''	O
(	O
1993–1994	O
)	O

Śródka	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Poznań	I-LOC

Eugene	B-PER
Aram	I-PER
,	O
the	O
18th	O
century	O
scholar	O
and	O
murderer	O
lived	O
here	O
.	O

''Pass	B-ORG
It	I-ORG
On	I-ORG
''	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Dave	I-ORG
Holland	I-ORG
album	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
,	O
2008	O

Northwest	B-ORG
Samar	I-ORG
State	I-ORG
University	I-ORG

The	O
ship	O
was	O
finally	O
commissioned	O
in	O
June	O
to	O
serve	O
on	O
the	O
American	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
West	I-ORG
Indies	I-ORG
Station	I-ORG
.	O

Direct	B-ORG
Fly	I-ORG
(	O
2005–2007	O
)	O

'	O
''	O
KSDX-LD	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
29	O

River	B-LOC
Cam	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Gloucestershire	I-LOC

Changes	B-ORG
''	O
(	O
2011	O
)	O

''Этюд	B-ORG
в	I-ORG
творчестве	I-ORG
ленинградских	I-ORG
художников.	I-ORG
Выставка	I-ORG
произведений.	I-ORG
Каталог	I-ORG
''	I-ORG
.	O

Jean-Baptiste	B-ORG
Massillon	I-ORG
(	O
1717–1742	O
)	O

``	O
Human	B-ORG
Nature	I-ORG
''	O
was	O
released	O
as	O
the	O
fourth	O
and	O
final	O
single	O
from	O
''Bedtime	O
Stories	O
''	O
in	O
June	O
1995	O
.	O

''	O
Wipe	B-ORG
Out	I-ORG
''	O
–	O
The	B-ORG
Surfaris	I-ORG

Max	B-PER
Krilich	I-PER
(	O
1982–1983	O
)	O

16px	O
2008	B-ORG
/	I-ORG
2009	I-ORG
-	O
with	O
Lokomotiv-Belogorie	B-ORG
Belgorod	I-ORG

Ty	B-PER
Lawson	I-PER
,	O
Indiana	B-ORG
Pacers	I-ORG

Ipomoea	B-LOC
pandurata	I-LOC
''	O
—	O
bigroot	O
morning-glory	O

Israel	B-PER
&	I-PER
New	I-PER
Breed	I-PER
(	O
''Live	O
From	O
Another	O
Level	O
''	O
,	O
2004	O
)	O

He	O
played	O
with	O
Jerry	B-PER
West	I-PER
and	O
Elgin	B-PER
Baylor	I-PER
.	O

From	O
2007	O
to	O
2015	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Costa	B-ORG
Rica	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
ambassador	I-ORG
to	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
United	I-ORG
Kingdom	I-ORG
.	O

``	O
Some	O
paintings	O
by	O
Cy	B-PER
Twombly	I-PER
have	O
had	O
this	O
term	O
applied	O
to	O
them	O
.	O

Patricia	B-PER
Crowther	I-PER
(	I-PER
caver	I-PER
)	I-PER

Leroy	B-PER
F.	I-PER
Meyers	I-PER

''	O
Joseon	B-LOC
(	I-LOC
Korea	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
''	O
'	O
–	O
Sukjong	B-PER
(	O
1674–1720	O
)	O

Robbie	B-PER
Merrill	I-PER
,	O
Godsmack	B-ORG
bassist	O

Claudio	B-PER
Cardozo	I-PER
(	O
Vida	B-ORG
)	O

The	B-ORG
Hope	I-ORG
Blister	I-ORG
-	O
...	B-ORG
smile	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
OK	I-ORG
''	O

Daniel	B-PER
Gallant	I-PER
,	O
writer	O
,	O
producer	O
and	O
director	O
of	O
Nuyorican	B-ORG
Poets	I-ORG
Café	I-ORG

It	O
moved	O
to	O
Brownwood	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Texas	I-LOC
on	O
1	O
June	O
1941	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
participated	O
in	O
the	O
VIII	B-ORG
Corps	I-ORG
Brownwood	I-ORG
Maneuvers	I-ORG
until	O
13	O
June	O
1941	O
.	O

Patrick	B-PER
Joseph	I-PER
Dillon	I-PER
,	O
Fr	O
.	O

*Matthews	O
Urgent	O
Care	O
(	O
located	O
in	O
Matthews	B-LOC
)	O

It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
Guinea-Bissau	B-LOC
.	O

His	O
first	O
cousin	O
is	O
Wesley	B-ORG
Hoolahan	I-ORG
.	O

''	O
Medicine	B-ORG
Hat	I-ORG
News	I-ORG
''	O

Slavyanka	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Primorsky	I-LOC
Krai	I-LOC
,	O
Russia	B-LOC

:	O
''Voiced	O
by	O
:	O
''	O
Midori	B-PER
Katō	I-PER

Following	O
his	O
conversion	O
in	O
January	O
1805	O
,	O
William	B-PER
Clowes’s	I-PER
preaching	O
was	O
testimony	O
and	O
“exhortation”	O
.	O

Jim	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Jesse	I-ORG
recorded	O
and	O
performed	O
the	O
song	O
in	O
the	O
early	O
1970s	O
.	O

Lao	B-LOC
Xả	I-LOC
Phình	I-LOC

''	O
Mr.	B-ORG
Soft	I-ORG
''	O
-	O
3:19	O

'	O
''	O
Kristen	B-PER
Stewart	I-PER
''	O
'	O
(	O
born	O
1990	O
)	O

They	O
were	O
later	O
reestablished	O
in	O
the	O
1940s	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Pontifical	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Salamanca	I-ORG
.	O

St	B-ORG
Ann	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Bryant	B-PER
Dunston	I-PER
(	O
5.0	O
)	O

Waterhouses	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
Durham	I-LOC

Stoke	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Cheshire	I-LOC
East	I-LOC

Dillard	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
;	O
(	O
155,000	O
sq	O
.	O

Mont	B-LOC
Brulé	I-LOC
(	O
3,538	O
m	O
)	O

Alexandre-Vincent	B-PER
Pineux	I-PER
Duval	I-PER
,	O
after	O
August	B-PER
von	I-PER
Kotzebue	I-PER

Oobi	B-ORG
''	O
,	O
2003	O

Gonzalo	B-PER
Fernández	I-PER
de	I-PER
Traba	I-PER
(	O
died	O
1160	O
)	O

His	O
family	O
migrated	O
from	O
Virginia	B-LOC
to	O
Kentucky	B-LOC
when	O
he	O
was	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Missouri	B-LOC
when	O
he	O
was	O
12	O
.	O

Raytheon	B-ORG
,	O
Ball	B-ORG
Aerospace	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Technologies	I-ORG
Corp	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
and	O
Boeing	B-ORG
were	O
developing	O
the	O
sensors	O
.	O

Star	B-ORG
Lake	I-ORG
Hydroelectric	I-ORG
Generating	I-ORG
Station	I-ORG

Jan	B-PER
Berg	I-PER
(	I-PER
Finnish	I-PER
footballer	I-PER
)	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1985	O
)	O

Fort	B-LOC
McPherson	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Nebraska	I-LOC

This	O
is	O
a	O
decrease	O
in	O
total	O
population	O
of	O
1.2	O
%	O
,	O
a	O
loss	O
of	O
361	O
people	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
census	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
2000	I-ORG
.	O

Ponce	B-ORG
de	I-ORG
León	I-ORG
Hotel	I-ORG
,	O
St.	B-LOC
Augustine	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Florida	I-LOC
,	O
1885–87	O
,	O
now	O
part	O
of	O
Flagler	B-ORG
College	I-ORG

from:02	O
/	O
13	O
/	O
2007	O
till:02	O
/	O
07	O
/	O
2008	O
color	O
:	O
MR	O
text	O
:	O
''	O
M.	B-ORG
Romney	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
R	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
''	O

``	O
Venezia	B-ORG
''	O
,	O
by	O
Hombres	B-ORG
G	I-ORG

William	B-PER
Foyle	I-PER
–	O
founder	O
of	O
Foyles	B-ORG
bookshop	O

Kevin	B-PER
Poulin	I-PER
(	O
1-0-1	O
)	O

Paul	B-PER
Ayshford	I-PER
Methuen	I-PER
,	I-PER
4th	I-PER
Baron	I-PER
Methuen	I-PER

TV	B-ORG
Guide	I-ORG
''	O
named	O
her	O
No	O
.	O

Eskimo	B-ORG
Joe	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
video	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

The	O
first	O
,	O
“Conditioning	O
and	O
Learning”	O
,	O
jointly	O
authored	O
with	O
Donald	B-PER
Marquis	I-PER
,	O
was	O
very	O
widely	O
cited	O
up	O
until	O
the	O
1960s	O
.	O

Eurovision	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
Greatest	I-ORG
Hits	I-ORG
''	O

Jamshedji	B-ORG
Bomanji	I-ORG
Wadia	I-ORG
built	O
''Minden	O
''	O
in	O
1810	O
.	O

''	O
The	O
Second	O
Person	O
''	O
,	O
poems	O
(	O
Four	B-ORG
Way	I-ORG
Books	I-ORG
,	O
2007	O
)	O

''	O
You	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Me	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2013–present	O
)	O

Ryan	B-PER
Dempster	I-PER
,	O
P	O
,	O
2004–12	O

''High	B-ORG
Lonesome	I-ORG
''	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Country	I-ORG
Gentlemen	I-ORG
album	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

R5	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Henry	B-PER
May	I-PER
(	I-PER
VC	I-PER
)	I-PER

The	O
building	O
was	O
constructed	O
to	O
Leed	B-ORG
Gold	I-ORG
standards	O
.	O

War	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
Bone	I-ORG
Thugs-n-Harmony	I-ORG
song	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

''	O
Maho	B-ORG
Tsukai	I-ORG
ni	I-ORG
Taisetsu	I-ORG
na	I-ORG
Koto	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2008	O
)	O

All	O
tracks	O
composed	O
by	O
Tom	B-PER
Browne	I-PER
,	O
except	O
where	O
indicated	O

Sir	B-PER
Owen	I-PER
Wynn	I-PER
,	I-PER
3rd	I-PER
Baronet	I-PER

The	O
Central	B-ORG
Committee	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
CPSU	I-ORG
and	O
,	O
more	O
specifically	O
,	O
its	O
Politburo	B-ORG
,	O
set	O
basic	O
guidelines	O
for	O
planning	O
.	O

Bobbie	B-PER
Nelson	I-PER
and	O
Willie	B-PER
Nelson	I-PER
–	O
How	B-ORG
Great	I-ORG
Thou	I-ORG
Art	I-ORG
''	O

Brownsville	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Wisconsin	I-LOC

Michael	B-PER
David	I-PER
Irving	I-PER
Gass	I-PER

Maurus	B-PER
von	I-PER
Schenkl	I-PER

He	O
was	O
drafted	O
12th	O
overall	O
by	O
the	O
Saskatchewan	B-ORG
Roughriders	I-ORG
in	O
the	O
2012	B-ORG
CFL	I-ORG
Draft	I-ORG
.	O

Moravia	B-LOC
(	I-LOC
canton	I-LOC
)	I-LOC

House	B-ORG
Majority	I-ORG
Whip	I-ORG
(	O
2005–2013	O
)	O

''	O
I	B-ORG
Do	I-ORG
n't	I-ORG
Wan	I-ORG
na	I-ORG
Live	I-ORG
My	I-ORG
Life	I-ORG
Like	I-ORG
You	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1995	O
)	O

''	O
(	O
2016	O
)	O
,	O
Daptone	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG

Maryland	B-ORG
Route	I-ORG
302	I-ORG

Edward	B-PER
King	I-PER
,	O
later	O
Bishop	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Lincoln	I-LOC

Kaleń	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Gmina	I-LOC
Rawa	I-LOC
Mazowiecka	I-LOC

List	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
MLB	I-ORG
all-time	I-ORG
leaders	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
doubles	I-ORG

Center	B-LOC
Township	I-LOC
,	O
Cloud	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Kansas	I-LOC

He	O
spent	O
his	O
early	O
childhood	O
in	O
Cork	B-LOC
.	O

Psy	B-ORG
–	O
appeared	O
and	O
danced	O
to	O
his	O
``	O
Gangnam	B-ORG
Style	I-ORG
''	O
on	O
stage	O
with	O
host	O
Kevin	B-PER
Hart	I-PER
while	O
he	O
introduced	O
the	O
next	O
presenters	O

Audio	B-ORG
Stream	I-ORG
Input	I-ORG
/	I-ORG
Output	I-ORG

Araxxe	O
is	O
based	O
in	O
Lyon	B-LOC
,	O
France	B-LOC
and	O
was	O
founded	O
in	O
2005	O
.	O

Investors	B-ORG
in	I-ORG
People	I-ORG

Larry	B-PER
Cheney	I-PER
Rube	B-PER
Marquard	I-PER
NYG	O

'	O
''	O
National	B-ORG
Women	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
Service	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

Paraphrase	O
by	O
Dmitri	B-PER
Shostakovich	I-PER

He	O
moved	O
to	O
Logan	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Utah	I-LOC
in	O
1861	O
.	O

Aluisio	B-PER
Neres	I-PER
–	O
Rapid	B-ORG
–	O
2004–2005	O

3	O
April	O
-	O
Liverpool	B-LOC
defeated	O
Newcastle	B-ORG
United	I-ORG
4-3	O
.	O

1992	O
)	O
Toronto	B-ORG
city	I-ORG
councillor	I-ORG
and	O
Chair	O
of	O
the	O
Toronto	B-ORG
Transit	I-ORG
Commission	I-ORG

Gunnar	B-PER
Knudsen	I-PER
(	O
1848–1928	O
)	O

NWA	B-ORG
/	I-ORG
UPW	I-ORG
/	I-ORG
Zero1	I-ORG
International	I-ORG
Junior	I-ORG
Heavyweight	I-ORG
Championship	I-ORG

Barwick	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Georgia	I-LOC

National	B-ORG
Museum	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Marine	I-ORG
Biology	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Aquarium	I-ORG
-	O
Taiwan	B-LOC

All	O
compositions	O
by	O
Thelonious	B-PER
Monk	I-PER
except	O
as	O
indicated	O
.	O

It	O
was	O
officially	O
announced	O
at	O
an	O
event	O
held	O
by	O
Famitsu	B-ORG
on	O
August	O
26	O
,	O
2014	O
.	O

Nans-sous-Sainte-Anne	B-LOC
(	O
25420	O
)	O

Shkodër	B-ORG
Orthodox	I-ORG
Cathedral	I-ORG

Euro	B-LOC
Plus	I-LOC
Pact	I-LOC

Sen.	O
Kent	B-PER
Conrad	I-PER
(	O
Budget	B-ORG
Committee	I-ORG
Chairman	O
)	O
,	O
D	B-ORG

'	O
''	O
South	B-ORG
Bend	I-ORG
Cubs	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

Many	O
of	O
the	O
high-ranking	O
leaders	O
of	O
Vietnam	B-LOC
were	O
detained	O
here	O
.	O

New	B-ORG
Masonic	I-ORG
Temple	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
St.	I-ORG
Louis	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Missouri	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

In	O
the	O
semifinals	O
,	O
he	O
faced	O
Will	B-PER
Martinez	I-PER
at	O
Bellator	B-ORG
114	I-ORG
on	O
March	O
28	O
,	O
2014	O
.	O

Disengage	B-ORG
the	I-ORG
Simulator	I-ORG

Johann	B-PER
Sebastian	I-PER
Bach	I-PER
-	O
Sheep	B-ORG
May	I-ORG
Safely	I-ORG
Graze	I-ORG

'	O
''	O
Anaphylactic	B-ORG
reaction	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

He	O
is	O
the	O
namesake	O
of	O
present-day	O
Langhorne	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Pennsylvania	I-LOC
,	O
which	O
adopted	O
his	O
name	O
in	O
1876	O
,	O
and	O
neighboring	O
Langhorne	B-LOC
Manor	I-LOC
.	O

*2006	O
:	O
Christchurch	B-ORG
Boys	I-ORG
'	I-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
and	O
King	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
College	I-ORG
(	O
tied	O
)	O

all	O
across	O
SFR	B-ORG
Yugoslavia	I-ORG
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
safe	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
happened	O
in	O
the	O
1970s	O
or	O
1980s	O
.	O

Miriam	B-PER
Mörsel	I-PER
Nathan	I-PER

*79	O
–	O
Jermaine	B-PER
Jones	I-PER
-	O
@	O
Saskatchewan	B-ORG
Roughriders	I-ORG
,	O
Sept.	O
29	O
,	O
2001	O

in	O
1967	O
from	O
the	O
West	B-ORG
Virginia	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
College	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Law	I-ORG
.	O

Portland	B-ORG
Brewing	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG

North	B-LOC
Brunswick	I-LOC
Township	I-LOC
,	O
Middlesex	B-LOC
County	I-LOC

10	B-ORG
Seconds	I-ORG
(	O
2010	O
)	O

Samaria	B-LOC
(	I-LOC
ancient	I-LOC
city	I-LOC
)	I-LOC

Paul	B-PER
Shaw	I-PER
—	O
FC	B-ORG
New	I-ORG
York	I-ORG
—	O
2011	O

Charles	B-PER
T.	I-PER
Akre	I-PER
–	O
investor	O
,	O
financier	O
and	O
businessman	O

2012–13	B-LOC
Liga	I-LOC
Nacional	I-LOC
Superior	I-LOC
de	I-LOC
Voleibol	I-LOC
Femenino	I-LOC

``	O
'	O
''	O
In	O
the	O
Cards	O
''	O
'	O
''	O
is	O
the	O
penultimate	O
episode	O
of	O
the	O
fifth	B-ORG
season	I-ORG
of	O
Star	B-ORG
Trek	I-ORG
:	I-ORG
Deep	I-ORG
Space	I-ORG
Nine	I-ORG
''	O
.	O

Back	B-ORG
to	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Bars	I-ORG
''	O

Johnson	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Vermont	I-LOC
–	O
William	B-PER
Samuel	I-PER
Johnson	I-PER

They	O
later	O
moved	O
to	O
El	B-LOC
Paso	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Texas	I-LOC
.	O

Islingby	B-ORG
IK	I-ORG
22	O
7	O
4	O
11	O
24-37	O
25	O
Relegated	O
?	O

*20px	O
Alabama	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Route	I-ORG
73	I-ORG

Bodø	B-ORG
/	I-ORG
Glimt	I-ORG
finished	O
third	O
and	O
defeated	O
Odd	B-ORG
Grenland	I-ORG
in	O
the	O
playoff	O
to	O
earn	O
promotion	O
.	O

Born	O
in	O
Charleston	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
South	I-LOC
Carolina	I-LOC
,	O
Charleston	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	O
South	B-LOC
Carolina	I-LOC

''	O
Alan	B-ORG
Carr	I-ORG
:	I-ORG
Chatty	I-ORG
Man	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2011	O
)	O

;	O
20px	O
Vendée	B-LOC
(	O
85	O
)	O

1970–1972	O
Odd	B-PER
Einar	I-PER
Dørum	I-PER

``	O
The	O
Intro	O
And	O
The	O
Outro	O
''	O
—	O
Bonzo	B-ORG
Dog	I-ORG
Band	I-ORG
(	O
1967	O
)	O

''	O
Uma	B-ORG
Thurman	I-ORG
''	O
-	O
Fall	B-ORG
Out	I-ORG
Boy	I-ORG

NCIS]]	O
''	O
,	O
Rizzoli	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Isles	I-ORG
''	O
)	O

It	O
is	O
a	O
subsidiary	O
of	O
Eneco	B-ORG
Energie	I-ORG
.	O

György	B-PER
Faludy	I-PER
(	O
poet	O
)	O

Miles	B-PER
Jupp	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1979	O
)	O
,	O
comedian	O

Minamoto	B-PER
no	I-PER
Yoshitomo	I-PER

Republic	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Formosa	I-ORG
(	O
1895	O
)	O

''	O
B.	B-ORG
J.	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Bear	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1979–81	O
)	O

Harry	B-PER
Hands	I-PER
(	O
1912	O
-	O
1913	O
)	O
(	O
first	O
term	O
)	O

''	O
'In	O
Green	B-ORG
Algae	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

Saurav	B-PER
Ghosal	I-PER
/	O
Harinder	B-PER
Pal	I-PER
Sandhu	I-PER

Raivo	B-PER
Seppo	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1973	O
)	O
,	O
writer	O

Jim	B-PER
Gott	I-PER
(	O
4	O
)	O

Peter	B-PER
Vack	I-PER
as	O
Will	O

Watkins	B-ORG
M.	I-ORG
Abbitt	I-ORG
(	O
D	O
)	O

Edward	B-ORG
M.	I-ORG
Purcell	I-ORG
–	O
1967	O

Some	O
episodes	O
were	O
repeated	O
on	O
BBC	B-ORG
Radio	I-ORG
7	I-ORG
in	O
2008	O
,	O
2010	O
,	O
2011	O
,	O
and	O
2012	O
.	O

November	O
12	O
:	O
Akihito	B-PER
is	O
enthroned	O
as	O
Emperor	B-PER
of	I-PER
Japan	I-PER
.	O

La	B-LOC
Esperanza	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Honduras	I-LOC
(	O
21,000	O
inhabitants	O
)	O

208	O
Wesley	B-LOC
Chapel	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Florida	I-LOC
$	O
25,897	O

Denise	B-PER
Laurel	I-PER
as	O
Chammy	O

Paweł	B-PER
Waloszek	I-PER
-	O
'	O
''	O
2	O
''	O
'	O
(	O
2,0	O
,	O
-,0	O
)	O

John	B-PER
Dickens	I-PER
(	O
1785–1851	O
)	O

It	O
consists	O
of	O
Ian	B-PER
Robb	I-PER
,	O
Ann	B-PER
Downey	I-PER
and	O
Shelley	B-PER
Posen	I-PER
.	O

Ultraman	B-ORG
Retsuden	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2011–present	O
)	O

He	O
then	O
moved	O
to	O
Fulham	B-ORG
who	O
were	O
managed	O
by	O
his	O
former	O
manager	O
Kevin	B-PER
Keegan	I-PER
,	O
where	O
he	O
made	O
28	O
appearances	O
in	O
two	O
separate	O
loan	O
spells	O
,	O
eventually	O
signing	O
for	O
them	O
permanently	O
.	O

Jimmy	B-PER
Greaves	I-PER
,	O
(	O
Chelsea	B-ORG
)	O
,	O
41	O

``	O
Islands	B-ORG
in	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Stream	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
featuring	O
Kenny	B-PER
Rogers	I-PER
)	O

They	O
play	O
at	O
the	O
18,810-capacity	O
Rogers	B-ORG
Arena	I-ORG
.	O

Goa	B-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Management	I-ORG
,	O
Goa	B-LOC

Richard	B-PER
Caborn	I-PER
(	O
1997–1999	O
)	O

Karl	B-PER
Marx	I-PER
and	O
Friedrich	B-PER
Engels	I-PER
contributed	O
to	O
the	O
paper	O
and	O
helped	O
in	O
editing	O
.	O

Tomorrow	B-ORG
is	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Long	I-ORG
Time	I-ORG

'	O
''	O
''Ten	O
Months	O
''	O
'	O
''	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
only	O
album	O
from	O
the	O
band	O
No	B-ORG
Tagbacks	I-ORG
.	O

Chairman	O
,	O
Royal	B-ORG
Opera	I-ORG
House	I-ORG
,	O
Covent	B-LOC
Garden	I-LOC
,	O
1974–1987	O

Slot	B-ORG
Machine	I-ORG
''	O
-	O
Midas	B-ORG
Interactive	I-ORG
Entertainment	I-ORG
(	O
2003	O
)	O

1975	B-ORG
:	O
Bryan	B-PER
Maxwell	I-PER
(	O
fourth	O
overall	O
)	O

It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
Australia	B-LOC
and	O
in	O
West	B-LOC
Papua	I-LOC
,	O
Indonesia	B-LOC
.	O

Nuovo	B-ORG
cinema	I-ORG
Paradiso	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1989	O
)	O

Uren	B-PER
,	I-PER
Malcolm	I-PER
(	O
1946	O
)	O
.	O

Everest	B-LOC
(	O
1997	O
)	O
.	O

Theoretically	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
possible	O
to	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
material	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
claims	O
this	O
material	O
was	O
already	O
made	O
,	O
including	O
claims	O
from	O
MIT	B-ORG
and	O
Harvard	B-ORG
.	O

Metal	B-ORG
Slug	I-ORG
X	I-ORG
2001	O
(	O
producer	O
)	O

He	O
was	O
traded	O
to	O
the	O
New	B-ORG
Jersey	I-ORG
Devils	I-ORG
in	O
1985	O
along	O
with	O
Rich	B-PER
Preston	I-PER
for	O
Bob	B-PER
MacMillan	I-PER
.	O

Southside	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
shopping	I-ORG
centre	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

''	O
MotoGP	B-LOC
''	O
'	O

Lady	B-ORG
Eleanor	I-ORG
Brandon	I-ORG
(	O
1519	O
–	O
27	O
September	O
1547	O
)	O
,	O
who	O
married	O
Henry	B-PER
Clifford	I-PER
,	I-PER
2nd	I-PER
Earl	I-PER
of	I-PER
Cumberland	I-PER
.	O

Alexander	B-PER
Myburgh	I-PER
(	O
1883	O
-	O
22.1.1884	O
)	O

Yusef	B-PER
Azizi	I-PER
Bani-Torof	I-PER
,	O
journalist	O
and	O
activist	O
.	O

Gore	B-PER
Verbinski	I-PER
/	O
Alan	B-PER
Silvestri	I-PER

'	O
''	O
Matthijs	B-PER
Büchli	I-PER
''	O
'	O

Scărița	B-LOC
River	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
Dezna	I-LOC
)	I-LOC

Hannity	B-PER
&	I-PER
Colmes	I-PER
''	O

93	O
of	O
the	O
Sons	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Confederate	I-ORG
Veterans	I-ORG
.	O

Since	O
January	O
2005	O
the	O
STPI	O
also	O
has	O
participartory	O
status	O
at	O
the	O
Council	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Europe	I-ORG
.	O

the	O
Fine	B-ORG
Arts	I-ORG
Museums	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
San	I-ORG
Francisco	I-ORG
,	O

'	O
''	O
Bedfordshire	B-ORG
County	I-ORG
Football	I-ORG
League	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

Ninth	B-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Force	I-ORG
,	O
21	O
March	O
1946	O

''	O
Love	B-ORG
Is	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Losing	I-ORG
Game	I-ORG
''	O

Patriarch	B-PER
Alexy	I-PER
I	I-PER
of	I-PER
Moscow	I-PER
,	O
ruled	O
in	O
1945–1970	O

The	B-LOC
Park	I-LOC
Estate	I-LOC

Calvin	B-PER
Peete	I-PER
(	O
3	O
)	O

Ar	B-ORG
Rumaylah	I-ORG
Southwest	I-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Base	I-ORG
(	O
Abandoned	O
1991	O
)	O

Franck	B-PER
Fréon	I-PER
(	O
1995	O
)	O

Meşeli	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Şavşat	I-LOC

exe	B-PER
exist	O
,	O
then	O
foo.com	O
will	O
always	O
be	O
executed	O
first	O
.	O

For	O
his	O
efforts	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
elected	O
to	O
his	O
first	O
career	O
Pro	B-ORG
Bowl	I-ORG
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
drafted	O
as	O
a	O
return	O
specialist	O
but	O
contributed	O
on	O
offense	O
,	O
recording	O
3	O
carries	O
for	O
42	O
yards	O
and	O
6	O
catches	O
for	O
79	O
yards	O
.	O

He	O
also	O
left	O
behind	O
11	O
grandchildren	O
including	O
grandson	O
Steve	B-PER
,	O
and	O
14	O
great-grandchildren	O
.	O

Sami	B-PER
Yaffa	I-PER
(	O
Hanoi	B-ORG
Rocks	I-ORG
,	O
New	B-ORG
York	I-ORG
Dolls	I-ORG
,	O
Murphy	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
Law	I-ORG
)	O

It	O
is	O
a	O
registered	O
charity	B-ORG
.	O

|	O
'	O
''	O
Comox	B-ORG
Valley	I-ORG
Glacier	I-ORG
Kings	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

He	O
moved	O
at	O
age	O
one	O
to	O
Modena	B-LOC
.	O

(	O
See	O
Fountains	B-ORG
in	I-ORG
Paris	I-ORG
)	O
.	O

20	O
November	O
2006	O
-	O
'	O
''	O
The	B-ORG
Kooks	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
/	O
Plan	B-PER
B	I-PER
/	O
Get	B-PER
Cape.	I-PER
Wear	I-PER
Cape.	I-PER
Fly	I-PER

4	O
-	O
Greentree	B-ORG
Stable	I-ORG
(	O
1943	O
,	O
1950,1952	O
,	O
1953	O
)	O

0-3	O
José	B-PER
Mamede	I-PER
(	O
90	O
)	O

Pachysandra	B-LOC
''	O
Michx	O
.	O

Shirley	B-PER
Horn	I-PER
–	O
Here	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
to	I-ORG
Life	I-ORG
''	O

He	O
is	O
the	O
nephew	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
NBA	B-ORG
player	O
James	B-PER
Hardy	I-PER
(	O
Utah	B-ORG
Jazz	I-ORG
)	O
.	O

(	O
National	B-ORG
Standard	I-ORG
Time	I-ORG
–	O
UTC+8	B-ORG
)	O
''	O

``	O
You	B-ORG
're	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Bad	I-ORG
Way	I-ORG
''	O
by	O
Saint	B-ORG
Etienne	I-ORG
(	O
1993	O
,	O
No	O
.	O

Johnnie	B-PER
Lee	I-PER
Wills	I-PER
(	O
1912–1984	O
)	O

``	O
Number	B-ORG
One	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Alexia	I-ORG
song	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
''	O
-	O
3:47	O

There	B-ORG
Goes	I-ORG
Another	I-ORG
Love	I-ORG
Song	I-ORG
–	O
Outlaws	B-ORG
–	O
3:05	O

*Lost	O
works	O
of	O
Posidonius	B-PER
.	O

''hypoleium	O
''	O
(	O
habit	O
,	O
William	B-ORG
O.	I-ORG
Douglas	I-ORG
Wilderness	I-ORG
)	O

Aldo	B-PER
Martínez	I-PER
HernándezReplacing	I-PER
Fernando	B-PER
de	I-PER
las	I-PER
Fuentes	I-PER

:	O
Zenit	B-ORG
Leningrad	I-ORG
,	O
/	O
Dynamo	B-ORG
Kiev	I-ORG
,	O
Logroñés	B-ORG
,	O
Valencia	B-LOC
,	O
Rangers	B-ORG
,	O
Istanbulspor	B-ORG

He	O
was	O
born	O
at	O
Buenos	B-LOC
Aires	I-LOC
.	O

Minoo	B-PER
Akhtarzand	I-PER
(	O
2010-present	O
)	O

*Southeast	O
:	O
Juramento	B-LOC
,	O
Glaucilândia	B-LOC

St.	B-ORG
Thomas	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Greenville	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
RI	I-ORG

In	O
1997	O
Patriarch	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Moscow	I-ORG
Alexei	I-ORG
II	I-ORG
attempted	O
to	O
visit	O
a	O
ROCOR	B-ORG
held	I-ORG
monastery	I-ORG
in	O
Hebron	B-LOC
with	O
Yasser	B-PER
Arafat	I-PER
.	O

'	O
''	O
Jenna	B-PER
Jameson	I-PER
''	O
'	O

+	O
Member	O
,	O
California	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Assembly	I-ORG
:	O
1974-1978	O

Despite	O
the	O
single	O
's	O
success	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
included	O
on	O
Quarantine	B-ORG
the	I-ORG
Past	I-ORG
:	I-ORG
The	I-ORG
Best	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Pavement	I-ORG
.	O

It	O
was	O
built	O
with	O
the	O
unusual	O
gauge	B-ORG
of	O
.	O

'	O
''	O
Ballsh	B-LOC
''	O
'	O

*2004	O
``	O
Mr.	B-ORG
M	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
single	O
)	O

''	O
'	O
''	O
Jonny	B-ORG
Zero	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
''	O

**	O
''	O
Kingdom	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Pamplona	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
–	O
Sancho	B-PER
I	I-PER
(	O
905–925	O
)	O

*AIADMK	O
=	O
All	B-ORG
India	I-ORG
Anna	I-ORG
Dravida	I-ORG
Munnetra	I-ORG
Kazhagam	I-ORG

His	O
daughter	O
and	O
grandson	O
subsequently	O
worked	O
for	O
Bury	B-ORG
F.C	I-ORG
.	I-ORG

Sigismond	B-PER
Thalberg	I-PER
(	O
1855	O
)	O

A	O
supporter	O
of	O
Mohamed	B-PER
Morsi	I-PER
,	O
he	O
was	O
arrested	O
after	O
the	O
2013	B-ORG
Egyptian	I-ORG
coup	I-ORG
d'état	I-ORG
.	O

Rik	B-PER
Grashoff	I-PER
–	O
990	O

Pingju	B-LOC
(	O
评剧	O
)	O
(	O
Hebei	B-LOC
)	O

*1769	O
:	O
Carlo	B-PER
Ignazio	I-PER
Monza	I-PER

Kunchacko	B-PER
Boban	I-PER
,	O
Unni	B-PER
Mukundan	I-PER

Jay	B-PER
McShann	I-PER
,	O
Muskogee	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Oklahoma	I-LOC

Fire	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Snow	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2008	O
)	O

In	O
1996	O
he	O
matriculated	O
in	O
the	B-ORG
Moscow	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
Faculty	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Journalism	I-ORG
,	O
from	O
which	O
he	O
graduated	O
in	O
2002	O
.	O

Sir	B-PER
David	I-PER
English	I-PER
,	O
journalist	O
and	O
Editor	O
of	O
the	O
Daily	B-ORG
Mail	I-ORG
''	O
from	O
1971–92	O

'	O
''	O
Tony	B-PER
Thorpe	I-PER
''	O
'	O

He	O
was	O
a	O
recipient	O
of	O
Yale	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
's	O
Sanford	B-ORG
Medal	I-ORG
.	O

Talu	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Chaharmahal	I-LOC
and	I-LOC
Bakhtiari	I-LOC

Narda	B-ORG
(	O
Kamikazee	B-ORG
)	O
(	O
performed	O
with	O
Gian	B-PER
Magdangal	I-PER
)	O
-	O
August	O
222	O

22px	O
'	O
''	O
Tuva	B-ORG
Republic	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

Atlantic	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG
,	O
however	O
,	O
wanted	O
a	O
second	O
,	O
more	O
well-known	O
guitarist	O
to	O
join	O
the	O
band	O
,	O
and	O
Al	B-PER
Pitrelli	I-PER
was	O
chosen	O
.	O

Leskovac	B-LOC
(	I-LOC
Knić	I-LOC
)	I-LOC

*2000	O
:	O
'	O
''	O
Nejmeh	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
-	O
Shabab	B-ORG
Al-Sahel	I-ORG

He	O
began	O
his	O
career	O
in	O
2008	O
in	O
the	O
Heartland	B-ORG
F.C	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
,	O
before	O
moving	O
the	O
following	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
Sunshine	B-ORG
Stars	I-ORG
F.C	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
.	O

'	O
''	O
Amanda	B-PER
Coetzer	I-PER
''	O
'6–3	O
,	O
6–2	O

He	O
was	O
named	O
after	O
his	O
late	O
maternal	O
grandfather	O
,	O
David	B-PER
Gardiner	I-PER
.	O

``	O
Among	O
the	O
results	O
was	O
the	O
1967	O
Asaba	B-ORG
massacre	I-ORG
.	O

Alfred	B-PER
D'Orsay	I-PER
Tennyson	I-PER
Dickens	I-PER
(	O
1845–1912	O
)	O
,	O
lecturer	O
on	O
the	O
life	O
of	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
Charles	B-PER
Dickens	I-PER

He	O
played	O
in	O
the	O
National	B-ORG
Hockey	I-ORG
League	I-ORG
for	O
the	O
Hartford	B-ORG
Whalers	I-ORG
.	O

'	O
''	O
Black	B-ORG
Sails	I-ORG
at	I-ORG
Midnight	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
''	O

**	O
Marc	B-PER
Gasol	I-PER
–	O
Memphis	B-ORG
Grizzlies	I-ORG

Barbara	B-PER
Mensing	I-PER
Cornelia	B-PER
Pfohl	I-PER
Sandra	B-PER
Wagner-Sachse	I-PER

Top	O
Design	O
Top	B-ORG
Design	I-ORG
''	O

'	O
''	O
A.J.	B-PER
Henderson	I-PER
''	O
'	O

Nicole	B-PER
Briscoe	I-PER
:	O
(	O
2015–present	O
)	O

It	O
was	O
released	O
in	O
June	O
1988	O
as	O
the	O
first	O
single	O
from	O
the	O
album	O
Highway	B-ORG
101	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Volume	I-ORG
2	I-ORG
''	O
.	O

Albert	B-ORG
Van	I-ORG
den	I-ORG
Berg	I-ORG

The	O
Animal	B-ORG
Liberation	I-ORG
Front	I-ORG
claimed	O
responsibility	O
for	O
the	O
attack	O
.	O

Richard	B-PER
Burton	I-PER
,	O
Elizabeth	B-PER
Taylor	I-PER

During	O
the	O
Nazi	B-ORG
Occupation	I-ORG
,	O
Mustafa	B-ORG
Kruja	I-ORG
and	O
Shefqet	B-PER
Vërlaci	I-PER
would	O
encourage	O
him	O
of	O
taking	O
a	O
more	O
active	O
role	O
.	O

Fedde	B-ORG
Le	I-ORG
Grand	I-ORG
-	O
'	O
''	O
Winner	O
''	O
'	O

Metelen	B-ORG
Land	I-ORG
station	I-ORG

Napoleon	B-PER
in	O
a	O
guest	O
appearance	O

``	O
The	B-ORG
Cigarette	I-ORG
Duet	I-ORG
''	O

Coleman	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
D'Alton	I-ORG
Cory	I-ORG
,	O
CPR	B-ORG
1942–1947	O
.	O

It	O
started	O
off	O
with	O
8	O
franchises	O
:	O
Charlotte	B-ORG
Sting	I-ORG
,	O
Cleveland	B-ORG
Rockers	I-ORG
,	O
Houston	B-ORG
Comets	I-ORG
,	O
Los	B-ORG
Angeles	I-ORG
Sparks	I-ORG
,	O
New	B-ORG
York	I-ORG
Liberty	I-ORG
,	O
Phoenix	B-ORG
Mercury	I-ORG
,	O
Sacramento	B-ORG
Monarchs	I-ORG
,	O
and	O
the	O
Utah	B-ORG
Starzz	I-ORG
.	O

4th	B-ORG
Virginia	I-ORG
Cavalry	I-ORG
(	O
detachment	O
)	O

On	O
6	O
August	O
2013	O
,	O
He	O
joined	O
Oita	B-ORG
Trinita	I-ORG
on	O
a	O
half-year	O
loan	O
from	O
FC	B-ORG
Tokyo	I-ORG
.	O

Campeonato	B-ORG
Mineiro	I-ORG
:	O
2010	O
,	O
2012	B-LOC

As	O
such	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
host	O
files	O
,	O
but	O
hosts	O
information	O
about	O
the	O
''location	O
''	O
of	O
these	O
files	O
in	O
an	O
indexed	O
torrent	B-PER
file	O
.	O

''	O
'Special	O
guests	O
:	O
'	O
''	O
Lena	B-PER
Gercke	I-PER
,	O
Collien	B-ORG
Fernandes	I-ORG
,	O
Katy	B-PER
Perry	I-PER
,	O
Kylie	B-PER
Minogue	I-PER

later	O
RNAS	B-ORG
Charlton	I-ORG
Horethorne	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
HMS	I-ORG
Heron	I-ORG
II	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Amesti	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
California	I-LOC

Sámal	B-PER
Pætursson	I-PER
Lamhauge	I-PER

(	B-ORG
17648	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
1996	I-ORG
UU	I-ORG

*11	O
Jarred	B-PER
Fayson	I-PER
-	O
''Sophomore	O
''	O

Image	O
:	O
San	B-LOC
Francisco	I-LOC
de	I-LOC
Macorís	I-LOC
section	O

Donald	B-PER
Gray	I-PER
(	O
1987	O
to	O
1998	O
)	O

The	O
ship	O
was	O
scrapped	O
at	O
Oakland	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
California	I-LOC
,	O
in	O
August	O
1961	O
.	O

Tony	B-PER
Peña	I-PER
,	I-PER
Jr	I-PER
.	I-PER

``	O
Turn	B-ORG
On	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Radio	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
January	O
2011	O
)	O

It	O
was	O
notified	O
in	O
The	B-ORG
Gazette	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
India	I-ORG
''	O
on	O
23	O
December	O
1966	O
.	O

Supreme	B-ORG
Court	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Republic	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
China	I-ORG

Peter	B-PER
Doherty	I-PER
-	O
``	O
Broken	B-ORG
Love	I-ORG
Song	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2009	O
)	O

Birmingham	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Warks	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
England	I-LOC

Yahoo	B-ORG
Screen	I-ORG
and	O
PBS	B-ORG
were	O
added	O
on	O
November	O
19	O
,	O
2013	O
.	O

It	O
is	O
also	O
used	O
by	O
some	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
SNM	B-ORG
.	O

North	B-LOC
Manitou	I-LOC
Island	I-LOC
,	O
part	O
of	O
Sleeping	B-LOC
Bear	I-LOC
Dunes	I-LOC
National	I-LOC
Lakeshore	I-LOC

He	O
was	O
an	O
alumnus	O
of	O
Nebraska	B-ORG
Wesleyan	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
.	O

It	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
The	B-ORG
CW	I-ORG
Plus	I-ORG
and	O
can	O
be	O
seen	O
exclusively	O
on	O
Charter	B-ORG
.	O

''	O
According	B-PER
to	I-PER
Jim	I-PER
''	O
(	O
2001–2009	O
)	O

*2013	O
:	O
``	O
Water	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Flame	I-ORG
''	O
-	O
Loved	B-ORG
Me	I-ORG
Back	I-ORG
to	I-ORG
Life	I-ORG
''	O
,	O
Celine	B-PER
Dion	I-PER

Brett	B-PER
Atwood	I-PER
,	O
print	O
and	O
online	O
journalist	O
.	O

The	O
first	O
building	O
at	O
that	O
location	O
was	O
probably	O
built	O
in	O
the	O
early	O
13th	O
century	O
by	O
the	O
Rudolf	B-LOC
II	I-LOC
von	I-LOC
Rapperswil	I-LOC
.	O

Jacques	B-PER
Caffieri	I-PER
,	O
sculptor	O
(	O
born	O
1678	O
)	O

Cusseta	B-LOC
and	O
Chattahoochee	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Georgia	I-LOC

*Drums	O
–	O
Guillermo	B-PER
E.	I-PER
Brown	I-PER

Berkeley	B-PER
L.	I-PER
Bunker	I-PER
(	O
D	O
)	O

:	O
'	O
''	O
''Top	O
4	O
''	O
'	O
''	O
:	O
``	O
Teddy	B-ORG
Bear	I-ORG
''	O
and	O
``	O
Jailhouse	B-ORG
Rock	I-ORG
''	O
by	O
Elvis	B-PER
Presley	I-PER

Mario	B-PER
Praz	I-PER
(	O
introduction	O
)	O

Rochdale	B-ORG
Cricket	I-ORG
Club	I-ORG

Nino	B-PER
Baragli	I-PER
-	O
Per	B-ORG
amore	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
solo	I-ORG
per	I-ORG
amore	I-ORG
''	O

'	O
''	O
Year	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Spider	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
''	O

William	B-PER
Boyd	I-PER
(	I-PER
writer	I-PER
)	I-PER

*20px	O
Texas	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Highway	I-ORG
278	I-ORG
(	O
former	O
)	O

The	O
role	O
of	O
Ellen	B-PER
G.	I-PER
White	I-PER
's	O
writings	O

The	O
plaque	O
was	O
installed	O
on	O
Bascom	B-ORG
Hall	I-ORG
in	O
1915	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
remains	O
.	O

1975	O
Atlantic	B-LOC
City	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
New	I-LOC
Jersey	I-LOC

Lady	B-PER
Gaga	I-PER
–	O
``	O
Marry	B-ORG
the	I-ORG
Night	I-ORG
''	O

Charles	B-PER
Spence	I-PER
Bate	I-PER

He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Hackney	B-LOC
,	O
London	B-LOC
and	O
died	O
in	O
Lewisham	B-LOC
.	O

The	O
role	O
was	O
most	O
notably	O
performed	O
by	O
Judith	B-PER
Light	I-PER
beginning	O
in	O
November	O
1977	O
.	O

Showstopper	O
(	O
48	O
Vol-au-vents	B-ORG
(	O
two	O
types	O
)	O
)	O

''	O
Kate	B-ORG
Plus	I-ORG
8	I-ORG
''	O

Miguasha	B-LOC
Group	I-LOC
/	O
Escuminac	B-LOC
Formation	I-LOC

Tryggvi	B-PER
Guðmundsson	I-PER
''	O
(	O
FH	B-ORG
)	O
''	O

In	O
2009	O
,	O
she	O
appeared	O
on	O
All	B-ORG
Star	I-ORG
Mr	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Mrs	I-ORG
''	O
with	O
her	O
then-fiancė	O
Michael	B-PER
Underwood	I-PER

(	O
Jason	B-PER
Gardener	I-PER
,	O
Marlon	B-PER
Devonish	I-PER
,	O
Christian	B-PER
Malcolm	I-PER
,	O
Mark	B-PER
Lewis-Francis	I-PER
)	O
38.32s	O
'	O
''	O
Q	O
''	O
'	O
(	O
SB	O
)	O

Maestranza	B-ORG
de	I-ORG
caballería	I-ORG

He	O
became	O
Port	B-ORG
Admiral	I-ORG
at	I-ORG
Plymouth	I-ORG
in	O
1783	O
.	O

''None	O
qualified	O
''	O
(	O
Australia	B-ORG
eliminated	O
by	O
Uruguay	B-ORG
)	O

Singers	O
:	O
Ileana	B-ORG
Cotrubas	I-ORG
,	O
Edita	B-ORG
Gruberova	I-ORG
,	O
Peter	B-PER
Schreier	I-PER
,	O
Walter	B-PER
Berry	I-PER
,	O
Martti	B-PER
Talvela	I-PER
.	O

'	O
''	O
Most	O
Valuable	O
Player	O
:	O
'	O
''	O
Paul	B-PER
Conway	I-PER

Prelude	B-ORG
in	I-ORG
C	I-ORG
minor	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Chandramauli	B-PER
Kumar	I-PER
Prasad	I-PER

St	B-ORG
Anne	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
Academy	I-ORG

In	O
their	O
first	O
appearance	O
they	O
were	O
portrayed	O
by	O
Mary	B-PER
Ann	I-PER
Mobley	I-PER
and	O
Norman	B-PER
Fell	I-PER
,	O
respectively	O
.	O

Wayne	B-PER
Wilkins	I-PER
Cheryl	B-PER
Cole	I-PER
Tinie	B-PER
Tempah	I-PER

''	O
Sea	B-PER
Hunt	I-PER
''	O
(	O
2009-2012	O
;	O
2013–present	O
)	O

This	O
variant	O
was	O
first	O
explored	O
,	O
and	O
later	O
patented	O
,	O
by	O
Homer	B-PER
Ledford	I-PER
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
``	O
dulcijo	O
.	O

In	O
collaboration	O
with	O
the	O
Haight	B-ORG
Ashbury	I-ORG
Switchboard	I-ORG
it	O
had	O
intermittent	O
connections	O
with	O
the	O
Haight	B-ORG
Ashbury	I-ORG
Free	I-ORG
Clinic	I-ORG
.	O

1996–97	B-ORG
Ukrainian	I-ORG
Premier	I-ORG
League	I-ORG

Descriptive	B-ORG
writing	I-ORG
is	O
usually	O
used	O
to	O
help	O
a	O
writer	O
develop	O
an	O
aspect	O
of	O
their	O
work	O
,	O
e.g	O
.	O

Deerhead	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Kansas	I-LOC

Nobuhiko	B-PER
Takada	I-PER
-	O
(	O
PRIDE	B-ORG
)	O

Andy	B-PER
Daly	I-PER
(	O
6	O
appearances	O
)	O

Other	O
large	O
shareholders	O
in	O
recent	O
years	O
include	O
:	O
BT	B-ORG
Pension	I-ORG
Scheme	I-ORG
(	O
13	O
%	O
)	O
,	O
the	O
Abu	B-ORG
Dhabi	I-ORG
Investment	I-ORG
Authority	I-ORG
(	O
9.9	O
%	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
China	B-ORG
Investment	I-ORG
Corporation	I-ORG
(	O
8.7	O
%	O
)	O
.	O

'	O
''	O
Julián	B-PER
Castro	I-PER
''	O
'	O

''	O
Like	B-ORG
to	I-ORG
Get	I-ORG
to	I-ORG
Know	I-ORG
You	I-ORG
Well	I-ORG
''	O
-	O
4:42	O

Court	B-ORG
system	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Pakistan	I-ORG

The	O
role	O
was	O
recast	O
with	O
Kathy	B-PER
Bates	I-PER
.	O

26	O
November	O
2008	O
,	O
Hamburg	B-LOC

Kun-Woo	B-PER
Paik	I-PER
,	O
2010	O
.	O

Francis	B-PER
Mary	I-PER
of	I-PER
Camporosso	I-PER
,	O
O.F.M.	B-ORG
Cap	I-ORG
.	I-ORG

It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
Croatia	B-LOC
and	O
Russia	B-LOC
.	O

4,800	O
speakers	O
were	O
reported	O
in	O
1990	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
1998	B-ORG
tsunami	I-ORG
wiped	O
out	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
population	O
.	O

Isaac	B-PER
C.	I-PER
Singleton	I-PER
Jr	I-PER
.	I-PER
as	O
Commander	O
Karza	O

''	O
Steal	B-ORG
the	I-ORG
Light	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2013	O
)	O

ManTech	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
(	O
Fairfax	B-LOC
)	O

The	O
Nomina	B-ORG
Sacra	I-ORG
are	O
written	O
in	O
contracted	O
way	O
.	O

married	O
Archduke	B-PER
Karl	I-PER
Salvator	I-PER
of	I-PER
Austria	I-PER
;	O
had	O
issue	O
.	O

Oliver	B-PER
Reck	I-PER
took	O
over	O
.	O

Progressive	B-ORG
Labour	I-ORG
Party	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
,	O
several	O
political	O
parties	O

Na	B-PER
Moon-hee	I-PER
as	O
Ji-oh	O
's	O
mother	O

Annihilation	B-ORG
''	O
,	O
by	O
Philip	B-PER
Athans	I-PER
(	O
hardcover	O
,	O
July	O
2004	O
,	O
ISBN	O
978-0-7869-3237-5	O
;	O
paperback	O
,	O
August	O
2005	O
,	O
ISBN	O
978-0-7869-3752-3	O
)	O

Papeete	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
Tahiti	I-ORG
-	O
Fa'a'a	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Airport	I-ORG

*October	O
13	O
,	O
2015-	O
Peace	B-ORG
Center	I-ORG

The	O
record	O
was	O
eventually	O
surpassed	O
by	O
the	O
2012	B-ORG
UEFA	I-ORG
Women	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
Champions	I-ORG
League	I-ORG
Final	I-ORG
.	O

Taylor	B-PER
Swift	I-PER
(	O
featuring	O
Kendrick	B-PER
Lamar	I-PER
)	O
—	O
``	O
Bad	B-ORG
Blood	I-ORG
''	O

*An	O
episode	O
of	O
The	B-ORG
OCD	I-ORG
Project	I-ORG
''	O

17	O
June	O
–	O
Henry	B-PER
Lawson	I-PER
,	O
poet	O
and	O
short	O
story	O
writer	O
(	O
died	O
1922	O
)	O

Clarence	B-ORG
Skinner	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

''	O
Souls	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Black	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1990	O
)	O

1981	O
–	O
James	B-PER
Galway	I-PER

:	O
''	O
Stenopygium	B-LOC
''	O
Becker	B-PER
,	O
1922	O

Specimens	O
are	O
available	O
for	O
display	O
in	O
Chicago	B-LOC
,	O
Washington	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
London	B-LOC
.	O

Northwest	B-LOC
Territories	I-LOC
,	O
Canada	B-LOC

Split	O
with	O
:	O
Napalm	B-ORG
Death	I-ORG

Bethel	B-ORG
Woods	I-ORG
Center	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Arts	I-ORG

Junior	B-ORG
Boy	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
Own	I-ORG

Kickers	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
''	O
9	O
(	O
1987	O
)	O

The	O
album	O
also	O
became	O
a	O
commercial	O
success	O
in	O
Continental	B-LOC
Europe	I-LOC
,	O
where	O
it	O
charted	O
within	O
the	O
top	O
ten	O
of	O
twelve	O
countries	O
.	O

The	B-ORG
Jon	I-ORG
Spencer	I-ORG
Blues	I-ORG
Explosion	I-ORG
-	O
``	O
She	O
Said	O
''	O

American	B-ORG
Behavioral	I-ORG
Scientist	I-ORG
48	O
(	O
1	O
)	O
,	O
48-59	O
.	O

What	O
they	O
once	O
controlled	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
powerful	O
Nationalist	B-ORG
businessmen	O
like	O
T.V.	B-ORG
Soong	I-ORG
and	O
H.H.	B-ORG
Kung	I-ORG
.	O

Abbey	B-ORG
Mills	I-ORG
Mosque	I-ORG

**	O
Flag	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
State	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
New	I-ORG
York	I-ORG

''	O
The	B-ORG
Early	I-ORG
November	I-ORG
/	I-ORG
I	I-ORG
Am	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Avalanche	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2005	O
)	O

Ansar	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
Islam	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

The	O
others	O
being	O
the	O
13th	B-ORG
Motorized	I-ORG
Brigade	I-ORG
and	O
11th	B-ORG
Airmobile	I-ORG
Brigade	I-ORG
.	O

He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Palacios	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Texas	I-LOC
,	O
USA	B-ORG
,	O
but	O
lived	O
in	O
Greenville	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Texas	I-LOC
for	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
.	O

'	O
''	O
Wilmington	B-ORG
Bombers	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

1995	O
–	O
Up	B-ORG
All	I-ORG
Night	I-ORG
''	O

This	O
is	O
the	O
idea	O
of	O
a	O
Grothendieck	B-PER
universe	I-PER
.	O

'	O
''	O
Taryn	B-PER
Hemmings	I-PER
''	O
'	O

She	O
has	O
also	O
been	O
interviewed	O
on	O
NBC	B-ORG
.	O

He	O
also	O
led	O
the	O
Golden	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Warriors	I-ORG
of	O
the	O
NBA	B-ORG
for	O
two	O
seasons	O
,	O
from	O
2004	B-ORG
to	O
2006	B-ORG
.	O

Bobby	B-PER
Hatfield	I-PER
:	O
half	O
of	O
The	B-ORG
Righteous	I-ORG
Brothers	I-ORG
and	O
Rock	B-ORG
'n	I-ORG
Roll	I-ORG
Hall	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Fame	I-ORG
inductee	O

James	B-PER
L.	I-PER
Pugh	I-PER
(	O
D	O
)	O
,	O
from	O
November	O
24	O
,	O
1880	O

LT-0	O
(	O
1946	O
)	O
Cambridge	B-LOC
,	O
United	B-LOC
Kingdom	I-LOC

98th	B-ORG
Indiana	I-ORG
Infantry	I-ORG
Regiment	I-ORG

The	O
application	O
succeeded	O
before	O
Mr	B-PER
Justice	I-PER
Blake	I-PER
,	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
High	B-ORG
Court	I-ORG
.	O

Sales	B-ORG
Promotion	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
magazine	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Max	B-PER
Schreck	I-PER
,	O
Gustav	B-PER
von	I-PER
Wangenheim	I-PER
,	O
Greta	B-PER
Schröder	I-PER

It	O
was	O
released	O
on	O
October	O
11	O
,	O
2011	O
via	O
Vanguard	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG
and	O
Sugar	B-ORG
Hill	I-ORG
Records	I-ORG
.	O

Most	O
notably	O
,	O
in	O
Chicago	B-LOC
,	O
Miami	B-LOC
and	O
Palm	B-LOC
Springs	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
California	I-LOC
.	O

Its	O
main	O
inhabitants	O
are	O
local	O
Kabyles	B-ORG
.	O

(	O
December	O
10	O
,	O
2009	O
,	O
Kadokawa	B-ORG
Group	I-ORG
Publishing	I-ORG
,	O
ISBN	O
978-4-0489-5073-2	O
)	O

Čenej	B-LOC
(	O
Csenej	O
)	O

He	O
did	O
not	O
manage	O
in	O
1953	O
,	O
although	O
he	O
did	O
manage	O
the	O
Mount	B-ORG
Vernon	I-ORG
Kings	I-ORG
in	O
1954	O
.	O

''	O
Liga	B-ORG
Provincial	I-ORG
de	I-ORG
Coronel	I-ORG
Portillo	I-ORG
:	O
'	O
''	O

Membrey	B-LOC
(	O
70340	O
)	O

Versions	O
of	O
''TYPO	O
''	O
were	O
also	O
published	O
and	O
used	O
(	O
with	O
permission	O
)	O
by	O
Page	B-ORG
6	I-ORG
magazine	I-ORG
.	O

Mauricio	B-PER
Victorino	I-PER
from	O
Nacional	B-ORG

*Producer	O
–	O
Eric	B-PER
Bazilian	I-PER
,	O
Rick	B-PER
Chertoff	I-PER
,	O
Rob	B-PER
Hyman	I-PER

Alex	B-PER
Kingston	I-PER
as	O
Boudica	B-PER

It	O
is	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Bochum	B-LOC
Section	O
of	O
the	O
German	B-ORG
Alpine	I-ORG
Club	I-ORG
.	O

Sunner	O
was	O
an	O
occasional	O
contributor	O
to	O
Word	B-ORG
Ways	I-ORG
:	I-ORG
The	I-ORG
Journal	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Recreational	I-ORG
Linguistics	I-ORG
''	O
.	O

''Ring	B-ORG
''	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
The	I-ORG
Connells	I-ORG
album	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
,	O
1993	O

Pennsylvania	B-LOC
(	O
50,995	O
)	O

He	O
joined	O
Salisbury	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
in	O
February	O
2005	O
.	O

large	O
,	O
low-massed	O
Baronial	B-ORG
style	I-ORG
brick	O
structure	O
is	O
located	O
in	O
a	O
mixed	O
commercial	O
,	O
recreational	O
and	O
residential	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O

Abe	B-PER
Woodson	I-PER
plunged	O
for	O
a	O
score	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
lead	O
to	O
13-6	O
after	O
three	O
quarters	O
.	O

Anchor	O
tenants	O
include	O
Next	B-ORG
New	B-ORG
Look	I-ORG
and	O
Marks	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Spencer	I-ORG
.	O

Civil	B-ORG
Democratic	I-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
(	O
232	O
)	O

Bosna	B-LOC
(	O
in	O
Bosanski	B-ORG
Šamac	I-ORG
)	O

Paul	B-PER
McCartney	I-PER
(	O
on	O
``	O
Yesterday	B-ORG
''	O
)	O

Lincoln	B-ORG
Financial	I-ORG
Field	I-ORG
(	O
2	O
)	O

Became	O
Sandy	B-ORG
River	I-ORG
Railroad	I-ORG
1	O

Cyrestis	B-LOC
camillus	I-LOC
elegans	I-LOC

It	O
was	O
renumbered	O
as	O
.	O

Middle	B-ORG
Schools	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Arlington	I-ORG
County	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Virginia	I-ORG

Child	B-ORG
and	O
Adolescent	B-ORG
Psychology	I-ORG

**	O
''	O
Epitolina	B-LOC
larseni	I-LOC
''	O
Libert	O
,	O
2000	O

6774	O
)	O
in	O
Berlin	B-LOC
.	O

This	O
record	O
was	O
broken	O
by	O
Scott	B-PER
Robinson	I-PER
of	O
Hearts	B-ORG
in	O
April	O
2008	O
.	O

Lake	B-LOC
Herbert	I-LOC
G.	I-LOC
West	I-LOC

'	O
''	O
Wayamba	B-ORG
United	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

Endwell	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
New	I-LOC
York	I-LOC

Martin	B-PER
Miller	I-PER
as	O
Head	O
Waiter	O

Katerina	B-PER
Maleeva	I-PER
''	O
(	O
Third	O
round	O
)	O
''	O

:	O
Established	O
16	O
June	O
1924	O
(	O
as	O
:	O
115th	B-ORG
Observation	I-ORG
Squadron	I-ORG
)	O
;	O
operates	O
:	O
C-130J	B-ORG
Hercules	I-ORG
(	O
MAFFS	O
)	O

Franz	B-PER
Anton	I-PER
Maulbertsch	I-PER
(	O
1968	O
,	O
1974	O
)	O

University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Curaçao	I-ORG

The	O
story	O
is	O
based	O
in	O
Ise	B-LOC
,	O
Mie	B-ORG
prefecture	I-ORG
.	O

He	O
is	O
also	O
a	O
former	O
member	O
of	O
Malaysia	B-ORG
national	I-ORG
football	I-ORG
team	I-ORG
from	O
1999	O
until	O
2005	O
.	O

The	O
24	O
Blue	B-ORG
Square	I-ORG
Premier	B-ORG
teams	O
join	O
the	O
eight	O
winners	O
from	O
the	O
previous	O
round	O
.	O

Moby	B-PER
(	I-PER
DJ	I-PER
set	I-PER
)	I-PER

He	O
was	O
returned	O
as	O
the	O
member	O
for	O
Appleby	B-ORG
in	O
1784	O
,	O
sitting	O
until	O
1790	O
.	O

''	O
Baddest	B-ORG
Guy	I-ORG
Ever	I-ORG
Liveth	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2013	O
)	O

Kyriakos	B-PER
Matsis	I-PER
,	O
member	O
of	O
EOKA	B-ORG

John	B-PER
Taylor	I-PER
(	O
1873	O
)	O

'	O
''	O
Season	B-ORG
Eight	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

Geschwaderkommodore	B-ORG
''	O
of	O
Kampfgeschwader	B-ORG
54	I-ORG

Detourn	B-ORG
was	O
released	O
in	O
March	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
six	O
years	O
since	O
their	O
highly	O
acclaimed	O
debut	O
album	O
,	O
Visible	B-ORG
Idea	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Perfection	I-ORG
,	O
back	O
in	O
2007	O
.	O

*1350	O
-	O
Coleophora	B-LOC
quadruplex	I-LOC
''	O

197	O
Craftsbury	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Vermont	I-LOC
$	O
17,185	O

Karin	B-PER
Kschwendt	I-PER
''	O
(	O
First	O
Round	O
)	O

''Word	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Mouth	I-ORG
''	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Toni	I-ORG
Basil	I-ORG
album	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
,	O
1982	O

Sir	B-PER
Rod	I-PER
Eddington	I-PER
(	O
1963–1967	O
)	O
–	O
CEO	O
,	O
Cathay	B-ORG
Pacific	I-ORG
,	O
Ansett	B-ORG
Airlines	I-ORG
and	O
British	B-ORG
Airways	I-ORG
;	O
director	O
,	O
News	B-ORG
Corporation	I-ORG
;	O
Chairman	O
,	O
Infrastructure	B-ORG
Australia	I-ORG

*1924	O
-	O
J.	B-PER
Edgar	I-PER
Hoover	I-PER
is	O
appointed	O
director	O
of	O
the	O
Bureau	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Investigation	I-ORG
—	O
predecessor	O
to	O
the	O
FBI	B-ORG
.	O

28	O
July	O
2011	O
–	O
Kim	B-PER
Han-Seob	I-PER
–	O
Daejeon	B-ORG
Citizen	I-ORG

Alaska	B-LOC
Lake	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
East	I-LOC

Oriel	B-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
,	O
Crawley	B-LOC

Karya	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Lefkada	I-LOC

''Evolution	B-ORG
''	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Malo	I-ORG
album	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
,	O
1973	O

Étienne-Joseph	B-PER
Floquet	I-PER
(	O
1748–1785	O
)	O

Music	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Command	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Conquer	I-ORG
series	I-ORG

When	O
Robin	B-PER
Phillips	I-PER
became	O
Artistic	O
Director	O
in	O
1975	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
familiar	O
face	O
.	O

The	O
production	O
was	O
filmed	O
in	O
and	O
around	O
Bozeman	B-LOC
and	O
Livingston	B-LOC
.	O

It	O
was	O
held	O
at	O
the	O
Stadio	B-ORG
Olimpico	I-ORG
in	O
Rome	B-LOC
,	O
Italy	B-LOC
on	O
7	O
September	O
1985	O
.	O

The	O
United	B-ORG
States	I-ORG
Army	I-ORG
Armor	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
is	O
now	O
located	O
at	O
Fort	B-ORG
Benning	I-ORG
.	O

Hirst	B-ORG
v.	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
United	I-ORG
Kingdom	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
No.	I-ORG
2	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

In	O
1982	O
he	O
received	O
his	O
Ph.D.	O
at	O
the	O
Belgrade	B-ORG
Medical	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
.	O

Lucy	B-PER
Larcom	I-PER
,	O
poet	O

At	B-ORG
Home	I-ORG
with	I-ORG
Owen	I-ORG
